Fu Kang'an presents birthday gift
May the Queen Mother live forever
Arise
Empress Dowager
Empress Dowager This is the time of Kang'an's expedition to the west
Made from the golden crown of the enemy chief
Good news came for a birthday gift
Empress Dowager
He'shen presents birthday gift
Servent bows before the Emporer and Empress Dowager
Arise
Empress Dowager
Empress dowager please see that this is a hundred and zero
Hepu pearls strung together
Servant He'shen wishes the Empress Dowager a boundless life
such a big pearl
so
It's the first time I've seen it
Empress Mother, these pearls
are difficult to find a few in big households
He dear courtier can in one go
Offer 108 pieces shows filial piety
Thanks your majesty
Ji Yun Ji Xiao'lan Jin Xian present birthday gift
Lord Ji, your gift
Lord Ji, please
Many thankss
Presenting Empress Dowager's Birthday gift
Empress Dowager, long live your majesty!
Arise
Thank you, Empress Dowager
Ji Xiao'lan, your present must be
ingenious
To the Empress Dowager and Emperor
Ji Xiao'lan can't be like Heshen lord
such a big deal
I had to write it myself a birthday blessing
Please accept the Queen Mother
Ji Xiao'lan's calligraphy is famous all over the world
good, let's see
I obey
It is said that Mr Ji is honest and thrifty
It is true today
Let's see it
Even saving money
let's see it then
the emperor let you open
Obey the purpose
Ji Xiao'lan what do you mean by this, a blank paper?
Do you care about the Queen Mother?
Queen Mother's Birthday
Mr Ji would never be so rude
You must have forgot it somewhere
looking around
Looking for it, caught in the armpit
or hidden in the boots?
On the birthday of Empress Dowager Ji Xiao'lan, you should present a blank paper.
hey Lord He'shen help
what
help
carry over
This is what I dedicate to the Queen Mother
why do you carry it over
I know it was given by lord He
borrow it
be careful
many thanks
These are worth thousands of dollars.
I know
what are you doing
slowly lord He
Many thanks, Lord Heshen, come and put it down slowly
Lord Heshen step back and then step back again
Empress please look
i see it, the word "longevity"
The queen mother, this is what I gave to you
This Ji Xiao'lan is opportunistic
Heshen hates people
This is borrowing flowers to offer the Buddha
Thank you Lord He
Sister, what's wrong?
Officers coming to catch me everywhere
Sister, hide in the troupe to see who dares to touch you
Xiao'yue, help me save this stuff
What kind of book is this, I can't read
you have to promise sis
Don't lose this thing
I guarantee with my head
It's worth about thousands of heads
catch her
go Xiao'yue!
who dares to attack
Xiao'yue you just promised
it's more important than anything
Uncle, forgive our clumsiness, where did this come from?
Yeah, how did Haotian Palace change to Haolong Palace?
Dragon Girl
yeah this
please get up
Nanny, I came late
emperor
I finally waited in time for you
Nanny
not late, not late
Nanny, what do you have to say
I will do anything for you
the white lady...
You want me to find this white lady
He said she's the emperor's mother
what are you talking about, nanny
emperor
you have to be careful
Nanny Nanny
the white lady
Immediately summon Ji Xiao'lan to the palace
your majestyJi Xiao'lan is in Yunzhou
He's hosting the  bigQiuWei exam
The queen mother arrives
I heard the nanny passed away
The nanny pressed you since you were young. No wonder you hurt the dagger
I hear this bad news
I can't eat
The nanny will be laboured all her life, if she has any request left
Son should finish it for her
Nanny what did she say
The nanny said for son to find someone
Who?
the white lady
Mother, you know this person
I don't know, don't know
There
Come over here and raise your arms
take off the hat
take him away
no no
The lord is really sharp eyed
Even the cheating method will not be renovated
What a disappointment
Pull it down and hit him twenty times
take him away
next
take the next one
take away
Where are you going to stop and take off your clothes?
why
take off quickly
I will do it myself
take off
hurry up, hurry up, hurry up
When you need to use knowledge it is not enough
I passed at the top, I am the zhuangyuan scholar
look
what
The essay that I wrote, I am the zhuangyuan scholar
crazy
Mr. Wu Jing wrote a piece of Confucian history
a man Fan'jin became crazy even after
becoming a lower rank scholar
Not even passed, and this man is crazy
This student is obviously nervous
Check it out, you can't even use a pen
What's your name? Don't be nervous, take it slow
who are you
How dare you?
This is the palace's academic and political discipline Lord Ji
You are Ji Xiaolan
You know me?
Ji Xiaolan. It's like a big gong tied to your foot
Wherever you go make a loud fuss
Flattery is nice but not the time
This officer still has to be fair
I'll give you something cheap
Mr Ji, are you smart?
He asked me if I was smart
Really doesn't know anything
I'm afraid you won't understand the paper written by our Mo'chou
i don't understand
Is there anything this world, that I Ji Xiaolan
can't understand?
I tell you that as long as it is written in this ink
I can understand
Can you understand it if it's written in blood?
The imperial examinations is harmful, just went crazy person
It's a pity there's another madman here.
Crap essay crap essay
Writing this kind of article deserves punishment
This article is well written
Apart for this bad word, fail
Lord, the government sent invitations
asking you to a banquet
Banquest, no thanks
The people of the government office specially explained
Lord Wu is inviting tonight Yunzhou's
best actor to play at the venue
Best actor? Who?
Du Xiao'yue
Du Xiao'yue never heard of them
thank you Lord Wu for me
Just say I couldn't go
There could be the pillars of the country here
Let's not be complacent, go reply
lord
Mr Ji, please come over
what's wrong?
Ji lord has come
Mr Ji you see
Which student's paper is this?
It's written in blood
volume written in blood
I'm afraid you won't understand the paper written by Mo'chou
Can understand it written in blood?
I remembered this guy's name is Mo'chou
You search for local inns now
Arrest of Mo'chou, further trial
before the lord came
Lord Wu captured a criminal called him Mo'chou
But she couldn't have gone to the exam.
Someone must have been an impostor on purpose
impostor
Why would he replace a criminals
Mr Ji burn this
It's outrageous that something like this happens
Not only students have to be killed
Even the chief examiner can't help but feel guilty
we all have to sit together
I know this
I want to know what else you guys have to say
Burn this roll and take another roll
As long as you don't do anything, it should go by calmly
Make big things small,  make small things trivial
Mr Ji can no longer hesitate
Just when I get the chance to hide in Yunzhou Mansion
I thought I could escape the capital's problems
Unexpectedly, there are ghosts everywhere
Prepare a sedan chair for me, I want to go to the government office to watch a play
the white lady she is the emperor's biological mother
Your Majesty, you are a Han Chinese
master master
The play is over, we should go
i want to meet the white lady
Hey, San'er, did you here you are headlining the first show tomorrow?
But don't get it wrong
Er'kui Ming'er, you are second
Did you hear? don't make a mistake
You all heard it, didn't you know?
Two gents, this is backstage, leave if you have no business
we know we know we know
Our prince thinks the play was very good
wants to look around, look around
please please please
you are the white lady
I am Du Xiaoyue
Du Xiaoyue
Yes
Where's Du Xiaoyue, Du Xiaoyue?
Master, Master, Master
Our prefect lord has a banquet tonight
Came specifically to hear Du Xiao'yue singing
How about you have to move now?
I'm going
Everyone, play the musical instruments and take the clothes
Hurry up to hear, no hurry
Why do you need an instrument?
Play the qin, can you sing without a qin?
Walk
who are you
I am Xu Xian
Lord Wu has a person named Mo'chou, you know
Mo'chou
The one locked up in your government's prison?
i want to see her
You can't see her Mr Ji
why
This woman is a rebel against the Qing Dynasty and the Ming Dynasty
The imperial envoy lord Fu Kang'an
arrived in Yunzhou to personally supervise the beheading
If the lord sees her, it will inevitably lead to criticism
Fu Kang'an also came, how lively
Lord, you see tonight's entertainment is coming out
watch the play watch the play
Mo'chou
Don't mention that Mo'chou, Lord Ji
What is the name of the actor Lord Wu
She is Du Xiao'yue playing the white lady
Du Xiao'yue
Lord Wu, don't let her sing
let her come down to me
Ji lord, you are in a good mood
stop, stop, don't sing
Du Xiao'yue quickly remove the costume
come down to accompany the lord
Outrageous, she was singing fine and now she stops
This Ji Xiao'lan is a moralist in court
I didn't expect that once he is among the commoners
that the true character of the scholar shows
The emperor doesn't know anything, this is how the officialdom is now
Ji Xiao'lan is an official from the capital
It is customary for local officials to treat them well.
Lord, they changed it again
This call to Hujiazhuang is not bad.
Lord Ji Xiao'yue is here
Lord Ji
come, come, sit, sit
sit close sit close
Xiao'yue serve Lord Ji
Pack your glory and wealth
Mr Ji to marking exam papers must be hard work
I toast the lord one cup
The papers are hard to read. I don't understand
Mr Ji is really joking, you're a genius
How can there be an article in the world that you can't understand?
Some articles I just don't understand
You can understand it using heart
using heart?
Yes, a heart that loves people
Well said, let's drink to that
Master, Master, don't be too angry
Ji Xiao'lan is well received by Yunzhou Prefecture
If he doesn't appreciate it, he will offend people
Lord Mo'chou is innocent
drink, drink, drink
while listening to the play, let's drink
Come on, tell me what's going on
Xiao'yue can't discuss it
Lord please take me to see Mo'chou in prison
You're not Mo'chou?
No she's my sister
I can't figure this out either.
It's better for the lord to ask her about it
ok
Don't believe me but I'm an academic
This scholar cannot go to visit the jail
Lord Wu
The girl you found Mr Ji is just his type
You see how good they are
Seems like a good old friend
He'shen. Ji Xiao'lan doesn't look just like socialising
How do you say that Ji Xiao'lan is also human?
It seems to be very popular
How many corrupt officials have I dealt with
Many of them use this
phrase to plead innocence
It seems that the officials of my Qing Dynasty are human beings
but common people are not human
master, quiter
The master is entertaining in the officialdom and making a scene
Ji Xiaolan can't be completely blamed
You are also pleading innocence for him
That's not what I mean, servant is telling the truth
people who are now officials
There are also reasons for being an official.
Lord Wu
Lady Xiao'yue
Lord Wu, Xiao'yue toasts you
You have to drink Xiao'yue's toast
Lord, I see the white lady
not the one you were looking for
she is too young
no no no you see where this is the white lady
It's just like Pan Jinlian
Good good
Mr Ji here
what
have another drink
Simply unsightly
I can't drink anymore I can't
Lord Wu, I'm a little too drunk
I want to go first
Mr Ji, you didn't drink much
Alcohol is not intoxicating, people are self-intoxicating
Come on, come prepare the sedan
Send Lord Ji back
This Xiao'yue girl will send me home
Then I am going
walk slowly
I'm going ahead first
Master, what are you doing?
Ji Xiao'lan is being too disrespectful
You can't do this, you'll reveal your identity
Harmless flirtation is fine
But now he's taking it to far
Lord, don't get angry
Ji Xiao'lan. The scholar's true color is showing
The emperor's words are indeed spot on, a scholar's true colors
Ji Xiao'lan is a gentleman
right
see clearly
The token of the prefect Wu is not fake
Lord Wu has ordered that no one can see Mo'chou
Why would there be other people looking for her again today?
I said that you, the head of the prison, are really doing your job very well.
I really have to thank you
So I can go back to bed earlier
yes you go tell Lord Wu
He is going to have to do it himself
It's not my business now, also
Fu Kang'an is going to remove him from position
i don't care
I say, prison guard
Forty big paddles, you can't escape. let's go...
lord please go to jail please go to jail
What are you talking about, please go to jail, are you cursing me?
No, no, no, please visit the criminal, please visit the criminal
that's more like it
sister, sister, sister
Sister, this is the man from the Capital
Mr. Ji Xiao'lan
You are smoking Ji
yes it's me
You are the one who speaks for the people
Smoking Ji
cannot be faked
Sister Mr Ji read the blood script I wrote
No he's here, him. A good official
Lord Ji...
lady
sister
Get up, get up and talk
since last winter
We haven't had a rain
No harvest
Many people sell their sons and daughters
The court's disaster relief money and grain were embezzled by local officials
People didn't get a cent
Victims became too hungry to live
Robbed the grain truck but was framed as a violent
I fought my way out of a bloody road and beat the drums
little did I know
How would you know they would falsely accusing you of being
a traitor who rebelled against Fuming and then sentence you to death
how do you know sir
I know Mr Ji is the best
this trick it's not new
Mr Ji, you now know that my sister was wronged
hurry up and save her
I'm an academic and I have no power at all
You have no power, you have intelligence
Mr Ji. Mo'chou's personal life and death is of no consequence
But those villians are still taking fish and meat from the villagers
Sir, if you don't stand up for justice
People have no hope
the people are still about loyalty
How can I, Ji Xiao'lan, stand idly by?
sir
Mr Ji Yunzhou corrupt officials' law bending
all of it has been recordedin a book
an account book
it was a conscientious money food master
He secretly recorded everything
Good teacher, what's his name?
His name is Huang Keming
the unspeakable things that the corrupt officials did
he knows it all
Mo'chou. Such important evidence
Why would he want to give it to you?
because
A sister is his soon to be wife
The virtuous couple is worthy of Ji Xiao'lan's admiration for asking for the people's life
The master is not asleep yet
The emperor is human too
all these years
Suddenly I found myself with another mother
another family
I can't sleep at night
The vast sea of ​​people. I only have this half piece of gold lock
When will you find your home?
The emperor's servant believes that you will find it
You are so sincere and God will be moved
Lord Heshen. the late supper is ready
I know, i'm coming
Your Majesty, you sit  here. Servant will go quickly and come back
What a delicious bun, how much is it?
three coins
Ji Xiaolan went to prison tonight to see Mo'chou
It's not what I expected
Immediately notify Fu Kang'an
one more bowl of wonton
Lord Ji, be careful here
Xiaoyue, you are very familiar with this Yunzhou
Are you from Yunzhou?
I've been sold since I was a kid until here
Growing up in an opera troupe
I don't even know who my parents are
do i have any siblings
What kind of person do you think I am?
Lord Ji, you see
don't move
government soldiers
How did the government soldiers know we were here?
I do not know either
Fu Kang'an
Mr Ji you really led the traitor here
It's you
I
Ji Xiao'lan, you betrayed me
no i won't go
Mr Ji here is a dangerous cave, stay for a long time and go
She is not a traitor
She is she is here to whistleblow
Be careful Xiao'yue
Mr Ji this is dangerous
take her away
Ji, The people of Yunzhou will never forgive you