Stop smoking, it smells
That's right, be fiercer
The shopkeeper will come up soon
Be careful when they come find you to pay
Who is it
I i
shopkeeper's
Come in
The shopkeeper is right to find him
He threw everything away.
Sir, everything is here, no less, no less.
You didn't open this thing, did you?
No, no inn rules
we can't touch the guests' items
Then what do you think I do
You, must be a business owner
Yes, I am a small business owner
Yes yes
shopowner, he broke all your stuff
You don't want him to pay?
stuff
These rotten things
I wanted to smash it a long time ago
coming, shopowner
Good shopowner
Sir, do these look good
Make do with it, so-so, let's use it
please make use
I'll send you some food as well later
I Know, I know
It's weird. There's something wrong with the people here.
The more you smash things, the nicer they are
How could this be? That's because you have a great presence.
My presence?
Open the door, open the door, open the door
Sleep like a dead pig. Open the door.
Who is it?
Sir, I am urgent to see you
annoying
Let him in
Brother-in-law brother-in-law
Lao Liu, you are too outrageous
You making fuss in the middle of the night, why?
Did your sister ask you to catch us?
It's not a big deal, I dare not
I wouldn't bother brother-in-law
A big deal. Yancheng has a big deal?
There are only big crap deals here
Brother-in-law, look
Heshen
Sir, who cares?
It's late at night.
Go, go. Servants!
master
Prepare the sedan chair, I'm going to the prefect's office
This is an official letter from He residence
This big print is the same
This print can't be fake, it must be Lord He's
Lord He Shen is here
Heshen is our protector
We have to be filial to him
Heshen is a big name but we've never seen him
Yeah, in the many years past
I haven't met with Lord Shen before.
Servants, civil and military officials of prefectures and counties
Go to the inn to pick up  our guest immediately
wait, sir
My lord, if a different office
Picks up Lord He Shen first
We will lose out
Yes, Lord He Shen is the emperor's favourite
Last time Lord He went to Shandong
That office was a bit too slow
You can change the color of this hat (demoted)
we can't be slow with Lord HE
But now he is posing as a commoner
Why is he living in an inn as a commoner?
it means Lord He
doesn't want officer to disturb him
Master has a point
The admiral of the Nine Gates, Lord He is famous for
But Lord He finds him tiresome
As a result, he threw out to plant trees.
Ah, it's bad if we go and bad if we don't
What do we do?
Calm down, everyone, don't worry
Listen to Master's insights
What Master Fan said
it's bad if we go and bad if we don't
The best policy
Send someone to get details
Exploring situation
It's decided, you go for a while first
I
Master Fan, I will accompany you
one military and the other civil, then I can relax
Royal Lord, eat more
I'm going spend my life in Yunzhou
and you're afraid I won't eat enough of this
Royal Lord, in my opinion, only if Qianlong
someone's coming
Lord He
Heshen greets the Royal Lord
You're welcome with Lord He
Thank you Lord
Lord He, please have tea
Thank you
Ah, how can tea be for the Royal Lord?
Come, come, I have a good Longjing here
Lady Four, please
Thank you, He Shen
Lady Four, wait
Tell me
Be sure to use the treasured mountain spring water
Its taste cannot be lost
ok
Lord He must not be here for tea
Why not get straight to the point
Royal Lord is really fast and quick to speak. that's unique
He Shen came here for an antique this time
antique
Royal Lord, please take a look at this antique piece of unknown origin
I need to consult Royal Lord
With Lord Shen, this
This half of the golden lock is related to the life of the emperor
Lord, I want to ask a question
The emperor, is he Han chinese?
The emperor is the biological child of the Emperor Yongzheng.
How can there be doubt about it?
But there is a lot of inner doubt
The emperor is inevitably be shaken.
I am the emperor's biological uncle
How can I not know
the Royal Lord is the prince of the Qing Dynasty
But this came from nanny's own mouth
The emperor has to believe it
This is out of nothing
How could this nanny say that?
It's a strange thing
It's because of this matter that the emperor
is posing as a commoner in Yancheng
If something were to happen, the great Qing Dynasty will be in turmoil?
Lord He Shen failed to stop the emperor going to Yancheng
you have failed
The prince blame is fair
But the emperor is even filial
to the ends of the earth
He has to find his birth mother
How can we stop him
Since it coudn't be stopped in advance
we can stop him now
If he can't find his birth mother, the emperor won't come back.
What is the priority between public and private?
What Lord said is fair
How can Mr He not understand this truth?
But the emperor himself has to be convinced
that he is Yongzheng's true son
then he will come back
I'm afraid he won't believe anyone now
Emperor won't believe us
But if the Royal Lord says it, the emperor will believe it.
I
Of course, the Royal Lord is the emperor's uncle
The emperor's life, the Royal Lord knows well
But the emperor has a decree. I can't leave
What is this
Holy decree, the emperor also has a decree
Don't let He Shen leave Yunzhou half a step
Royal Lord, if you go to Yancheng
He Shen will accompany you
Royal Lord, resist the decree, and I will accompany you to resist the decree
If the emperor cuts off the Royal Lord's head
My head will go too
Fate of the nation, everyone is responsible
Including the dignified Royal Lord
but
What is the priority between public and private?
Royal Lord, why don't you go with Lord He
Lady Four, this is men's business
Yes a man's business, Lord
Lord He
The emperor is in the safety of the world
The words of the Royal Lord are the emperor's peace
Don't behave like this in public
My lord, please get up
No I am kneeling for people
Lord
If something happens to the emperor, life will be lost.
The people of the world will suffer
Royal Lord, Lord He begs you on behalf of the people
Lord, please
I promise you
He Shen, on behalf of the people, thanks you Royal Lord
arrow shot well
Lady Four, let's compete
Lady, your arrow technique
It's really eye-catching
Brother Fu has high praise
I cannot be better than than your legendary swordsmanship?
Lady, don't go
Don't go to Yancheng
I know you are going to assassinate the emperor
Lady Four, promise me, stay in Yunzhou
Lord Fu, I can't leave the Fourteenth Lord
Lady Four, you can't leave me
Fourteenth Lord and Lord He are waiting
Lady Four, you can't go
Why, are you afraid I will die there
I'm afraid
I would not be me if I was afraid of death
Lady Four it's a traP
What trap?
You will die if you go to Yancheng
You mean this is Lord He's trap
Lady Four, you can't go
I will also not let you inform the fourteenth Royal Lord
Lady Four, Lady Four
finding his mother, is causing even Mount Hua to split apart
Xuxian, look at them
Xiaoyue, think before you speak
ok?
Xu Xian is worried that he can't find his mother
I forgot
Xu Xian, don't worry
it's just not having a mother?
You see, I don't even have a father
Xiaoyue
What I said is true
Mr Ji, your painting
I knew I can't hide the truth from you
I painted that picture myself
You know you can't hide it from me
Hasty forgery, unable to make it look aged
nothing like an ancient family heirloom
You always love to learn from Wu Dao
Can't hide it from the pen
This old Wu hurts me
Xu Xian, you're sneaky
You know the painting is fake
You don't make any fuss
I've been worried about it the whole time
Xiaoyue, what are you afraid of?
I'm afraid you want me to bring you my Master
Where can I find one for you?
It's weird, you know it's fake
Why do you want come with us to Yancheng?
Mr Ji painstakingly forged the antique
just to lure me to Yancheng
so I fulfilled his wish
I'm curious about it myself
curious
I wanted to see why Ji Xiaolan led me to the Yancheng
What exactly does he want?
You really look like a kid who can't grow up
Xiaoyue
Ah what's wrong
Although it's fake, this golden lock is real.
It's a nanny's object
Although the nanny is from Yunzhou
But her husband, Zheng Laoquan, is from Yancheng
And I also checked
This Zheng Laoquan is exactly a goldsmith
I have Zheng Laoquan's address here, take a look
Mochou go
Xu Xian, Xu Xian, you are so outrageous.
I just ordered food
You have to pay the bill if you want to leave.
Xiaoyue
Isn't Heshen here with you?
you don't need to pay the bill
people will rush to pay for him
Where are you going
Why are you pulling me
Let me tell you something, sit down
Do you know who this Xu Xian is?
Of course I know
Oh you know
Correct
Then he is
he is obviously the emperor
What's wrong?
too old
Why are you making such a fuss?
why are you making such a fuss?
There are errands around
Lord He, Lady Four is still not back
I'm a little worried
Royal Lord doesn't have to be, Yancheng is the place where she would get in trouble
The girl is prejudiced against the emperor
Maybe it's a good thing she's not coming
What  does Lord He think I want
Lord He
The Governor of Liangjiang has expedited documents
he reports floods
Royal Lord, this disaster relief is needed to save people.
Then I'll go to Yancheng first
Lord He is needed here to handle these duties
Then I will have to trouble you Royal Lord
Lord He, don't worry, I will go immediately.
Okay, then I will leave
Ok please
Lady Four
Doctor, my arrow really hit the target
Lord's legendary archery skills. Hit right in the shoulder
She'll be fine
But she has been in a coma for two days
what's going on?
Maybe she is in shock
Yeah, she didn't expect me to do it to her.
Wait I will prescribe her two medicines
heart medicine, we'll see if it works
As long as the doctor can cure her
No medicine is too expensive medicine
Yes
Lady Four
I pretended to be in a coma for two days and managed to trick you
Fu Kangan, you don't look like you've been through a lot of battles.
As long as you are okay
go
Lady, where are you going
I'm going to save the Fourteenth Lord
you
Ordered to issue 900,000 silver in the internal treasury
Hand it over to the top ministers
Distribution of eight and three flags
Make subordinate officials' operation generate interest
After you finished writing, use the official seal
Yes
That Ji Xiaolan
Leading the emperor to Yancheng
What kind of snake oil is he selling?
Send it back on the horse immediately
Sir
Why is there a problem over such a trivial matter?
My lord, look at this seal
My lord, look, look
seal
Ah, this seal
What's wrong with the seal
It's printed on
No, this is Ji Xiaolan's seal.
what
Is this seal real?
Who looks after the seal?
Me
How come this has happened
the emperor a few days ago
Before the emperor went to Yancheng
asked you to bring him the seal
Said it was to appreciate and appreciate
Do you know about this, my lord?
Yes, yes, I know, I know, I remember
The emperor sent someone
wanted to take my seal and play with it
have we not used it since?
No, after the emperor looked at it
I didn't look at it and put it away
Emperor
My lord, maybe the emperor made a mistake?
What mistake
The emperor put Ji Xiaolan's seal
in your seal box by mistake
No, how could the emperor make such a mistake?
What happened?
This is the great seal of a member of the imperial court.
How many important orders in the court are approved by me
Payment for forage and disaster relief from the Western Expedition
I use this seal all the time
How can the emperor mistake it
Besides, this kind of official seal is the same as any other
What is there to appreciate about it?
Could it be that the emperor intended to change them
My lord, what's the matter?
Ji Xiaolan's seal is with me
Mine is with him. He is now in Yancheng.
And the officials of Yancheng
Haven't even met me
My lord, Ji Xiaolan is pretending to be you.
good move
Notify Fu Kangan people to go to Yancheng as soon as possible
Yes
My lord, this is the inn
Sir, are you asleep?
What's wrong, sir?
I don't know how
as soon as I think about meeting Lord He
I have cramps in my legs and belly.
Bopin, you go in and have a look at Lord He
Let me stay outside and catch my breath
I haven't found Lord He
A thorn in the eye is delivered to the door
Guard all the doors
Look at my gestures and hit hard
Yes
What are you doing
one cannot avoid one's enemies
The mountains don't turn around, the water doesn't turn around, the roads don't turn around.
The road does not turn around
Do you know what place this is?
Oh, I don't know, sir, why don't you tell me?
I tell you this inn
It was opened by our county uncle and brother-in-law.
Oh, this is interesting
Brother-in-law, hello
Did you know that this is called?
what is it?
You mean provoking the lion
I'm in a good mood today
Let you off once
What are you doing
I'm comfortable sitting here
I feel very comfortable all over
Be careful I don't attack without mercy
Uncle Zhu, come here
Didn't you see I'm on official business?
Stop and no one can leave
Oh, I said sir
Your official position is eighth rank
But you have the presence of a top rank
You crawl under all the tables here for me
Or I won't spare you
Ah, sir, crawling under tables, must be fun
This Yancheng is a simple place, and official style is interesting.
friendliness is conducive to business success. don't lecture me
I won't talk about peace today.
Go crawl for me quickly
Only dogs crawl under tables
Don't worry, I'll let him
I won't let you crawl, how can I be willing to you?
Are you sick? Are you tearing up the calligraphy and painting?
Heshen, Lord Heshen
This tea tastes better now
Don't go
Didn't you just say I should drink with you?
I
You forgot, something about a lion?
provoking the lion
Remember, there is another saying there's always a way out.
Oh, by the way, I'll crawl under the tables first
Lord
Lord He, don't be angry, I'll crawl I'll crawl
My lord, my lord, bad news
Master Zhu made a big mess
What, don't scare me
It's true that Master Zhu made Lord He angry
he's being punished now
Lord He
My lord, go in help
let's go, go
Lord you can't leave
I'm not leaving, I can't afford it, I can hide
Go, go, go
Sir
This way this way
Emperor, I'll go to knock on the door
Mochou i'm afraid
The emperor is afraid
I'm afraid to see her
Who is she
the white lady, my birth mother
You dress as a commoner, travel a thousand miles
just to look for her
I'm afraid i'm afraid she's a Han chinese
No, I'm afraid I have Han blood
it doesn't matter what blood you have
It's all passed down to you by your mother
Han blood, Manchu blood
it's all red
But I am the emperor
Emperor and Commoner
we are all a child born to a mother
who doesn't accept their own birth mother
Go ahead, the white lady, she is waiting for you
emperor
Mochou Mochou
Emperor
It seems no one lives here
Excuse me, is this the Zheng family
yes Zheng family
where are they
Dead, all dead
Emperor
Who are you guys
Welcomes fourteenth Lord
Who told you to come? Get out of the way right away.
Fourteenth Lord, you have no other choice
Fourteen Royal Lord, you don't have a choice
Come with us
Palace officials are here. Who dares to be presumptuous?
don't bother, they won't come back
who were they?
I don't know either
Lady, are you okay?
I'm fine
I clearly hit your acupuncture points
sealed your meridians, how did you
I practice the tendon sutra
No one can hit my acupuncture points
Then you still pretended to be subjected to me
You could clealy fight back
But you pretended you couldn't move
I wanted to come to Yancheng with you
Lady Four, I'm worried about you
Fourteen Royal Lord has become a scapegoat
let him fall into the trap
You know this trap, you can save him
Lady Four, that's Lord He's trap
No one can save the Fourteenth Lord
can't save him then I'll die with him
Lady
Tell me how you contacted them
You say it quickly, say it quickly
listen
This is the signal
Who is the leader?
We are the Heaven and Earth Meeting against the Qing Dynasty and the restoration of the Ming Dynasty
Heaven and Earth Meeting
We know Qianlong is in Yancheng
Fourteen Royal Lord must be here to assassinate him
You know my whereabouts
Heaven and Earth will be willing to help the prince
No no
Fourteen Royal Lord was exiled by Yongzheng for how many years
This revenge should go to Yongzheng's son
take revenge
Your group of chaotic ministers
Fourteenth Lord
Our heaven and earth will take the anti-Qing Dynasty and the restoration of the Ming Dynasty as our mission
get rid of the Manchu in charge
But I have a common enemy with you
Our common enemy Qianlong
Qianlong is my nephew
Fourteen Royal Lord, the country is meant to be yours
Qianlong is posing as a commoner, in a weak position
Heaven and Earth will be willing to help Royal Lord remove him
afterwards the fourteenth Royal Lord will be emperor
You found the wrong person, I won't do it
Royal Lord it is now or never again
You will never have a chance to turn around
Farewell
Don't move
The Royal Lord has come now, but we can't let you leave
Mr. Ji, look, more gifts
I told you before, with me
there's food drink no problem
Strange you haven't even left
No one has come either
Why would people give you a gift?
You just don't understand this official business
If you want accurate information, to be well-informed
If you want to bow in time, you have to give gifts to not fall behind.
I heard people give gifts to officials.
Never heard of officials giving gifts to the people
you can buy the wrong thing
But you can;t give a gift wrong
When I was in Yunzhou
there was an official who was also dismissed
everyone ignored him
He picks up the junk on the street alone
This is also officialdom
Whether an official is corrupt or not?
we can only tell after he leaves
You just said that the garbage collector
Needless to say, not corrupt
Then Mr Ji
I think you must be corrupt
Why do you say that
Look at you, you are not an official now
yet there are so many people to send you gifts
Then if you become an official one day in the future,
Then you still have to rise three feet to the ground.
true, true
By the way, Xiaoyue
what do you think of my calligraphy
What does it say?
I forgot you can't read
this is handwriting I copied from Heshen
I think there is excellent likeness
not learning from a good person
why are you learning that bastard's handwriting
Chongsuo, I'm in Jingyou
You forget I am Heshen now
I have to write his words
that's right, your words do look alike
I don't just learn to write like him
If you remember in the fish warehouse, I can learn to speak like him
Fish, fish, big fish Fat Head
Sir and Lady it's time to eat
eating again?
waiter, bring two bowls of noodles
our shopkeeper
prepared a table and banquet are specially for the master
people inviting for food again
Madam, why don't you eat for nothing?
We can't refute the boss's kindness
lead the way
Oh, I'm so full
People are so kind, we can't not go
Walk, walk, walk
I don't think it's good to be an official, prone to gain weight.
Sir, lady here
Sir, do you have Lord He's old letters
here
Master, look at this writing
exactly the same
Yes, one person wrote both
Lord He
It's really Lord He Shen
I thought as soon as I saw him
rich and powerful official, can't be wrong
How do we both eat so much?
Don't worry
Someone will come to accompany us to eat soon
How do you know
someone's really coming
Liu Changfu, Prefect of Yancheng
Subordinates bow before see you and your wife
All four of you, get up, get up
No need to be polite
Thanks Lord
Come, come, take a seat, please enter
I'm here on a mission by the Emperor
Pretending to be a commoner, you cannot expose my identity to people
Yes yes
The banquet at this table is sumptuous
Lord deserves the food to make up for their hard work.
Yeah, of course
pretending to be a commoner
It's hard to eat, hard to sleep, it's really difficult
Madam, try this
Your chopsticks are dirty
How rude of me
I don't know if the emperor ordered my lord to make a private visit
How expensive is it?
My lord is the secret of the emperor
it is absurd ask
yes, my fault
You all, every year send me numerous gifts
Although we never met
But I count it in my heart
considering none of us are outsiders
It's good to have something to tell you.
The emperor ordered me to investigate Huang Keming's case this time.
I say you guys were too careless
How do you let this Huang Keming
go to Yunzhou
Sir, please relax
Then Huang Keming, he's a careless yob
Nonsense, Huang Keming is good man