Does Huang Keming know what I'm here for?
to kill me, right?
Wrong, I'm here to tell you a story
Back in the day, Emperor Kangxi had two princes
One is the fourth Lord Ziyong
When Lord Kangxi died
There are legends that the throne was to pass onto the fourteenth Lord
It was Emperor Yongzheng who changed it to the fourth Lord
That's just a rumor
But after Yongzheng ascended the throne
the fourteenth was most worried
And the first person to ordered under house arrest was also him
what's the royal business with me
After Qianlong ascended the throne
Did they release the fourteenth Lord
The Fourteenth Lord is currently in Yunzhou Mansion
If you have something to say, please say it directly
you can take all your crimes
and blame it all on the fourteenth Lord
what
What the emperor fears most is the usurper
As long as you say that all the crimes are the mastermind of the Fourteenth Lord
the emperor will definitely believe you
Then you can take it easy and be free
Huang Keming vindicates the people
I would never do that immoral thing
Huang Keming is a hero who knows current affairs
you can think about it
You also have a share of the government's corruption disaster food.
I've seen that ledger with your name on it
You are the real mastermind behind the scenes
I see that you refuse a toast only to drink a forfeit
Well, I will fulfill your wish
come
Send the rebels to the execution ground to be beheaded to the public
let go of me let go of me
Lord, spare him
Lord Wu, the imperial envoy patrols the kingdom on behalf of the emperor
You say I can't kill him?
That's not what I mean, look
who has no mother
My biological mother is probably in Yunzhou
she may be looking forward to
meeting her biological son
The emperor's filial piety
God will be moved
Mr. Ji, please help me find my biological mother
The people of Emperor Yunzhou
is living in the depths of ice and heat
The emporer's biological mother may also be there
Mr. Ji speaks with hidden meaning
Emporer, please take a look
sir this is
Emporer , this is an account book
It was preserved by Huang Keming at the risk of his death.
Also Du Xiaoyue
They took a risk to bring me to the opera in order to retrieve this
Look at the emperor
Please the emperor give back to the people in the disaster area
hurry up and hide
quick move it
This basket can't be moved
Why can't this basket be moved?
You can't move the fish behind me
I'm going to move it, move away
you see she can't
what is this
don't bother yourself
Girl, this book is very important
give it back to us
Xiaoyue, quickly open the account book
That's Huang Keming's ledger
fatso, why didn't you just say
I just tried it and wanted to tell
I was just about to tell...
,aybe I just don't want to tell you
No no no Xiaoyue don't fool around
Sir, do you want to let Huang Keming go?
You are crazy, if we let go Huang Keming
Your embezzlement of food for disaster relief
will all be exposed
I can't even protect you
There has been no news from the emperor recently
Was he be kidnapped too?
emperor
Get someone to identify this ring right now
Lord Fu, even you can't see the authenticity of this ring
Don't expect anyone else
Did you forget that there is still fourteenth lord
Fourteenth lord, but he is a criminal
The subordinate dare not see him
Only the fourteenth lord can tell if this is a royal item
If it's really the emperor, then it's an emergency
Don't be sad, Mr. Ji
That book will be destroyed.
It's probably God's will
Lord He, you can easily think past it
Okay, let's have fun
rejoice in pain
Yeah you see we have so many fish
Let's use fish as the theme, words flow from the mouth as from the pen of a master
Whoever can't keep up can be punished
using fish to make speeches?
I'll listen to Mr Ji
The emperor has approved , then I will go first
good
pass off the sham as the genuine
fish turns to dragon
fish... fish...
Lord Yu Heshen is calling the horses to stop
You think I can't keep up, listen up
Fish, big fish eat small fish, small fish eat krill
No literary interest, punish!
penalty! moving a basket
How could the dignified minister move the fish? Don't make trouble
Lord Heshen, you don't want the emperor to find his biological mother
What has the fish got to do with it?
certainly
Servant is going to move it
Hey, Lord Heshen, move the ones from there to here
ok let's go again
But this time louder
That's right, so the outside can hear. deliver letters
rafters for fish
Jiang Taigong's fishing volunteer takes the bait
It's alright now, I have a story
vulgar
punish again
What are the three of them doing in Xiaoyue
The three of them seem to be having a word battle
The fat guy loses every time
Watch them carefully, Brother Huang's life
relies on these three dogs
I know
let's go
get out of the way
drop car drop car drop car
lords please
Lord Wu, the prefect of Yunzhou, asked to see the Fourteenth Lord
please
Lady Four
Mr. Wu
please Lady Four
Wu has a request to see the Fourteenth Lord
Lord Fourteen is not feeling well today
What's the matter, just tell me?
This is not a small matter
I must ask the fourteenth brother to enlighten me
Of course, I have to ask the Lady Four to ask or me.
Wu will await respectfully
what's the matter
The prefect of Yunzhou sent this ring
Said it was no small matter
The owner of the ring has been taken by a group of kidnappers
Please identify it
Lord
the Emporer
the emporer?
This is the stuff of Emporer
This is the stuff of Lord Kangxi
this only passes to princes
It was passed on to Yongzheng and then...
The kidnapped hostage must be Qianlong
The kidnappers asked the government to hand over criminal Huang Keming
Otherwise, all three hostages will be executed
Don't these kidnappers know
that they have tied up the current emperor?
Lord, this is a God-given opportunity.
If Qianlong died, the world would be in chaos
Lord, you can make a comeback
no no no I'm old
This world should be yours
Kangxi's edict passed on the throne to Lord Fourteen
This ring was meant to be on your hand
Passed onto Lord Fourteen
don't mention it again
If not for Yongzheng usurping the throne
You were supposed to be sitting on the throne in the Qing Dynasty
Now the heaven has eyes to kill Qianlong with the hands of kidnappers
Lord, your revenge will be here
Lady Four
Lord, kidnappers demanded that the hostage be replaced by Huang Kepeng
as long as he dies
The hostages will be torn apart and Qianlong will die
Lord Heshen, take a break
Let's continue. dust has covered kitchen utensils and fish has spawned in cooking vessels because of long disuse
Longyang weeping fish
it is good
I. Fish slipped through the net
This sentence works
So no punishment, no punishment
No punishment, then he should be rewarded
Reward two crates of fish
Lord He, accept the reward
I accept
look lord
Does Lady Four and the Fourteenth Lord have any insight?
The Fourteenth Lord has seen it
It's a royal thing
But this is what Lord Shunzhi
gave to Concubine Dong back then
It was supposed to be a funerary item, but it's now here
Lord aid that he now owns this thing
Must be tomb robbers
Okay, let's go to the next sentence
fish carp jumping dragon gate
Well, this sentence is better reward again!
I accept the reward
Sea bass is nothing for beauty to fall into Chu captivity of empty Dai Nan Guanxue
Xiao Xiaopu heard the fish leaping across the forest waiting for the crane to return
feet, feet, you are so stupid
Ji Xiaolan, come up quickly
I can't go emperor
If you don't go, you wait to die, come quickly
if i go
People outside heard no sound inside the house
they'll break in
Then you won't be able to escape
Then when they found the two of us have gone
It's more dangerous for you to be here alone
take it easy, emporer
Ji Xiaolan has a plan to escape
Lord He, take the emporer away
Lord, let's go
If Ji Xiaolan does not go, I will not go
oh my lord, look at him
Your Majesty, don't you want to see your mother?
It's just about finding the biological mother
Emperor go, the world can't live without you
Emporer, the world is more important, filial piety is more important
big fish small fish fat head fish
Tanqing doubtful water shallow lotus moving to know fish scattered
it is good
monk knocking wooden fish
The wooden fish came out, it's really funny
Xiaoyue
sister
they're still talking about fish
listen
heavy punishment
You heard that fat guy lost again
They are really a group of scholars
yes there is one type of fish
They were trying to get it  right for a long time and they didn't get it right
what fish is that
salted fish
What is the stench all over your body?
We just came out of the fish warehouse
Master, you have the same smell
Ugh, how do we continue to wear this?
There is a clothes shop in front of the master
Can I change?
of course
then let's change
fire fire, the prison is on fire
Save people, save people, you stupid pigs
You're meant to be looking after the prison
what happened?
it's on fire
put out the fire!
Sir Huang Keming is still inside.
Huang Keming
Yes
Lord, Lord
hurry up
The fire is too big we can't save them
fool
Heshen get in the car
what ?
Driver quickly take us to the government office
This is Liu Yuanwai's car, leave!
master
get in the car
my car my car
Why are you sitting here? Get in
Sir, you just retired from working in the capital
good for you
It's all the grace of the emperor
This driver is he
Sir, who is in this car?
I don't know who is in car
I know  the driver was the emperor
Who dares to take a car when the emperor is a driver
Who is bigger than the emporer
I don't think you've ever been in a palace, have you?
no common sense
That driver is really the emperor.
The bright moon in the imperial hometown is like a dream fishing woodcutter
sister
The three dogs
still there
The government set fire to the prison Brother Huang burned to death
Brother Huang
Open the door and I'm going to kill them
To sacrifice to Brother Huang
where are the other two
you were meant to watch them
That's not right, they've been speaking this whole time
the three of them taking turns
Xiao Xiaopu Smells Fish Leaping Fish Dragon Listening to Brahma
Sea bass is beautiful and will not return
He can imitate, one person becomes three!
Then how am I meant to know
Scum officer, they left, you will die
Girl, when I die, Huang Keming cannot come back
Huang Keming is dead
Blood debt, blood to pay the dog officer, take your life
the universe is really trying to kill me
Girl, you can kill me
You have to let me understand why first
You tell me how Huang Keming died
As soon as they received my letter
they set the prison on fire
They say all prisoners in jail are dead
You didn't see Huang Keming's body
girl, listen to me
The two who escaped just now
It is indeed the official of the imperial court.
It's a high official and they will definitely come back to save me
as long as you keep me alive
Huang Keming may still be saved
Sister, maybe Brother Huang is not really dead.
Thirty right, right, begging for his blessing
So if Brother Huang hadn't died, we won't kill you
thank you girl
Sister, what do we do with this scum?
The officers and soldiers of the imperial court will come soon
you can't stay
take him away
Amitabha, you finally saved my life
you must save Huang Keming
Ji Xiaolan is still in their hands
They will send someone to replace Huang Keming
the emperor is wise
He lives, you live, he dies, you die
Fukang An dispatch a hundred elite soldiers to come with me
Come on, bring me all the famous doctors in the city
The emperor's entire city has been blocked and they can't escape
Ji "Big Tobacco Bag"
The emperor there are tabacco ashes here
Follow this road and find the ashes. Rewards for those who find it
there's ashes
wind is picking up
The emperor, it's windy, we can't find the ashes
back to the prison
The rain falls from the sky and the world is peaceful
Xiaoyue, what does your sister mean?
That's our code
Code, she's speaking in code,what do you want to do?
It means that...hey scum, stop snooping on our secrets
Okay, I don't ask
my name is tiger
Does tiger have any news about Big Brother Huang?
He's not dead, you can relax
Xiaoyue Brother Huang is not dead!
scum, you are very good at fortune telling. Brother Huang is not dead.
I heard, that's great
Since he isn't dead, can you stop calling me scum officer.
You should at least call me big brother once
Big brother, you wish
I don't deserve to be your big brother?
Huang Keming is my big brother
Indomitable heroism is not like you
ok then then I won't be your brother
Sister, we can use this scum officer
to go get Brother Huang
it is good
If it weren't for Fu Kang'an's heroic rescue
saving Huang Keming, then I would have filled this prison with you all
It was my inability to hold the prison, damn me
The emperor, the fire was suspicious
The fire didn't burn sooner nor later
Only as soon as the emperor's ring arrived
There must be someone who did this
Mr. Wu, who has seen this ring?
Fourteenth Lord
Then he should know this ring is mine
no, the fourteenth lord said
This ring was stolen by tomb robbers
stolen by tomb robbers
This is the stuff of Kangxi's ancestors
Why is he talking nonsense?
let me investigates the rebels
The clues are all implicated to the fourteenth Lord
fourteenth Lord uncle
Letting people burn Huang Keming is equivalent to putting the emperor to death
Fourteenth Lord is notorious
do not talk
The emperor rests his anger, as I see it
let's find out the whereabouts of Ji Xiaolan first.
Best way to rescue him
He Aiqing makes sense
I can send people to search
don't have to
No need, Huang Keming is not dead
They must exchange Ji Xiaolan
We just need to wait for news
Emperor is wise
Emporer, the thief shot another an arrow with a letter
leave
emporer
They want us to send Huang Keming out of the government office tomorrow
Emperor you really anticipated this
Wu Zui
minister here
How is Huang Keming now?
Emperor, Huang Keming was not burnt
After the doctor's diagnosis and treatment, there is no serious problem
Send Huang Keming out of the residence on time tomorrow
must not have any mistakes
I obey
Emperor, I lead a team to follow secretly
all can be captured
You can't beat the grass and startle the snake
Emperor, this Huang Keming is the leader of the rebels
Let the tiger return to the mountain and we'll suffer endless troubles
As long as Ji Xiaolan can return safely
I won't pursue their crimes
Sister, the street is quiet today
It's weird that the government is closed
is a little strange
Sister, look! Brother Huang
Thank goodness I was saved
big brother
Mochou
Brother Huang
You are Huang Keming who worked for the people's lives. Good man
Thanks
Brother, let's go
wait
who dares to move, he will die
move back
Lord Fu
back off
Brother Huang, let's go
Xiaoyue Brother Huang is back
i should get off
Letting you go now, aren't we courting death?
we'll let you go out of town
Get out of the city
don't chase
when do they invite me to their wedding toast
If you win the case
Big Brother Huang Big Brother Huang
scum officials! you let people go and still kill them
run, run, run
Brother Huang
It's so poisonous
what poison
This arrow is smeared with deadly poison
Brother Huang
Huang Keming, you have to hold on!
White lady is really a lady
since
Take that dog officer
Walk
Brother Ming. The government didn't let you live
I will  be the sacrifice of the scum officials to you today
Girls, this debt has a head and it must be paid
but I didn't shoot that poison arrow.
It was done by your people
Mochou
Do you know what two bird with one stone is?
that poison arrow
Obviously someone trying to hurt me
You should keep these words for Big Brother Huang.
I'll tell Big Brother Huang
before you let me die
I'll give him a blessing, okay?
Ask the scum officer to first kowtow to Big Brother Huang and confess his guilt
Huang Keming, Huang Keming
You are for the people in the disaster area
In my heart you are one good man
I, Ji Xiaolan, kneel down for you
Sister, he really knelt down
What the scum officer does in order to survive
Huang Keming, ah Huang Keming, although you are a good man
But the group of people you brought are stupid
who do you scold
Although the arrow hit you
the purpose was to kill me
The discerning person can see this
But some people just want to take this
they want to sacrifice my head to you
Be someone else's murder tool
Are you saying she's not an idiot?
Sister, he is scolding you
he is trying to change the rhetoric.
He is an official from the imperial court
this scum officer is not of low rank
If you kill the scum official, the court will be shocked
Only then can people in the disaster area have justice
Shanping County should have stockpiled food for disaster relief
ninety-three thousand six hundred and eighty-five
Now there is 36,232 stone eight less food
Baoyi County Baoyi County should have grain in stock
Thirteen thousand six hundred and thirty-two stone eight
Now less than eight thousand three hundred and sixty-two stone three
Sister, he is reciting the ledger
How much do you remember?
I have memorized all of Huang Keming's account books
How can you get it in two days?
I only need to read it once and I can remember it all
you're lying
why should i lie
Huang Keming gave me this ledger
I think it's important
So I take it very seriously
when i have time
I copied it down to present it to the emperor
This is hard evidence of corrupt officials
Sister, did you hear?
As long as this scum is here
Brother Huang's account book will be saved
It's impossible that no one could remember it all
But he just recited the account
Sister, don't kill him
let him rewrite the ledger
yeah so you can't kill me
if you kill me
Your big brother Huang's work will be in vain
Sister, then you really can't kill him.
Ji Xiaolan has no news yet
These kidnappers have no credibility, they won't let go
I knew that we shouldn't have let Huang Keming go.
But what Du Xiaoyue sings is the white lady
Will Ji Xiaolan be in the troupe?
There are one or two opera troupes in the north and south of Yunzhou.
If you add the amateur trupes, you will not be able to count.
we have to check them all but there is no Du Xiaoyue
I checked every one, but there is no du
But which opera house is playing The Legend of the White Snake now?
Coincidentally
None of opera houses are playing the white lady
I can't save Ji Xiaolan, I have failed as a man
Lord, you can see clearly
it's really him
Qianlong, he's so lucky
To escape from the kidnappers
He looks too much like Yongzheng
Lady Four, what are you going to do?
Lord, this is a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity
Can't kill Qianlong
You forgot how Yongzheng treated you
After Qianlong ascended the throne, he let me go
This bit of hypocrisy moved you?
why don't you think about it
The throne in the Qing Dynasty was originally yours
But the country is also the country of the Qing Dynasty
The Great Qing Dynasty
You see Qianlong travels in the mountains and waters
This country has become his playground
How does such an emperor govern the country in this way?
write quickly
Hey, I told you to write, did you hear me?
what am I writing?
Write out all of Brother Huang's ledger
girl, i haven't seen asking for help
as fierce as you
i am not asking you, i am ordering you
If you don't write, I will
kill me?
that won't work if I kill you
the ledger will be destroyed
let it be destroyed then
how about that
This is countless people's painstaking effort
how many people died for it
My sister said to bring down those dogs
and rescue hundreds of people  from the disaster area
All rests on this account. Write it now!
You also know that this ledger is so important
Then why are you are not more polite to me
Polite to you, scum officer, am I polite to you?
for this ledger
It's all in this scum official's head
With you being so threatening
Can't remember, can't write
Can't save the disaster area
you dare
Then what do you want to write it?
Xiaoyue
how about we go out to eat
In your dreams
You see how nervous I am these days
Shocked and frightened, my stomach hasn't had anything
Brain is all confused
can't remember
dogs officers are greedy
man
Sir, what do you have?
Make us a pot of good dragon tea
Okay
Lady Four you
How did Yongzheng treat his brother?
Let his son taste his own medicine tonight
you put in poison?
Sir, here is your tea
This tea is very good