Mr. Ji, look
don't move
palace soldiers
How did the palace soldiers know we were here?
I do not know either
Fukangan
Mr. Ji really lured the traitor
It's you
I
Ji Xiaolan, you betrayed me
no i won't go
Mr. Ji is here, it's dangerous to stay here, go
she's not a traitor
She is she is here to whistleblow
Be careful
Mr. Ji, this is dangerous
Xiaoyue
take her away
The people of Yunzhou will never forgive you
Why are you in an ambush here, Mr Fu?
After Mochou was arrested, we knew that in her hand
was a very important roster
But torturing her in every possible way just doesn't say anything
So we guess
As long as there are two people who Mochou believes in, go
She'll be sure to tell where the roster is hidden
you are using me
any person Du Xiaoyue bringsMochou must also trust
I just needed to follow Mr. Ji
You can catch them without any effort
Fukangan I tell you
That roster is not a roster of rebels
Mr. Ji, how do you know
That's the evidence of corrupt officials
Rebels certainly won't be on the roster
Write down that you want to refute
They will definitely make up their own names to cover their identities.
Mr. Ji as a scholar, you are too naive
Lord Fu, I Mr Ji might be a scholar
But I can tell the difference between good and evil
Du Xiaoyue, beautiful
made a fool of Ji the scholar
It's hilarious
ok i don't explain anything to you
but i tell you
Du Xiaoyue, she's innocent, let it go
Let her go? Ji Xiaolan, you're just scholar
This kind of thing is out of your hands
Well, it's not up to me
But it's up to the emperor
emperor
yes if you don't let go
Ji must report to the emperor
Okay, do you want to see the emperor?
ok, congratulations, majesty
one's own will
Ji Huang is immoral and immoral
Take off the top and get rid of the post for the people
white lady
Lord, we should go back
what do you say
white lady, who is she
Since the lady, she is the white snake Bai Suzhen
How can the white snake be my mother?
this. servant...
If there was someone who could solve this riddle
That person would be Ji Xiaolan
Master, sevant understands
Lord Ji, please get up
You called wrong, Lord He
This is only the commoner Ji Xiaolan
Come back
Let him go
Folks and fathers, I am Du Xiaoyue
what to shout
Xiaoyue Xiaoyue
Corrupt officials harm the people
You have to help me find justice
Brother, your fireworks are going to explode
How did this happen?
Throw it out, throw it out, throw it out
Brother-in-law, I know you'll come to my rescue
Sister, I've come to help you
Xiaoyue go!. the evidence is important. Go!
sister
go fast
Xiaoyue
scum officer is you
give me the ledger in your hand
I'll tear you apart
It's would be a pity to break such a good vase
god is so unfair
Such a good bottle is still broken
go fast
chase them for me
These scum soldiers
search for me
Xu Xian
How come there are so many soldiers
leave me alone
If you are caught, you will be implicated too
it's okay no problem
Do you know who I am?
Aren't you the white lady?
I'm a rebel, the official government is chasing me
The government is arresting you
yeah, scared right?
Don't be afraid, don't be afraid, come with me
do you know Fahai
That old monk?
I learned invisibility from him
Invisibility
can this work
OK, don't look at it, it won't work
give me a careful search
Heavenly and Earthly
and lord why are you here
I'll tell you later
What's with this woman, Lord Heshen Mr. Heshen?
Why did the emperor save her?
The emperor is looking for the white lady
white lady
Lord Heshen. That account book
That girl has it
If it was seen by the emperor...
The account books are insufficient, we have to worry about Ji Xiaolan
Ji Xiaolan has been dismissed, he's no bother
The general is wrong
The emperor will be angry for a while
He will dismiss Ji Xiaolan for a while
He will find that he cannot do without Ji Xiaolan
I understand that Lord Heshen is saying. goodbye.
Ji Xiaolan what will you do next?
Xu Xian, you really know magic
Those people really didn't see
do you really believe
That's because I wrapped you in a costume
Those soldiers saw me carrying a robe
They thought I was an actor too
Oh, those palace soldiers are so stupid
Xiaoyue, do you know the white lady?
Yes I play her
Don't you think I'm a bit like a white lady?
How can there be a white lady like you?
Xiaoyue, think about it carefully
Is there any actor who plays the white lady
who looks a bit like me but older than you
looks like you but older than me?
I think there is
she's a bit like you
what is her name
i don't know her name
I only know her alias
alias?
her alias is...
Xiaoyue
Come here
Sister, are you alright?
Who is he? what nonsense are you talking with him?
he is good
On his head is engraved the words "good man"
Sister, you don't know what he just saved me
Ajier knew that he had just
The villain pretends to be a hero to save the beauty
Lie to your trust, you know that
Your plays are all sung in vain
Xiaoyue, what is the white lady's name?
she seems to
What are you talking about, let's go
Xiaoyue
what is her alias
go
i forgot
go fast
Lord Fu
Lord Wu, do you know?
Someone is gossiping about you in front of the emperor
gossip what gossip
Someone secretly reported you to the emperor
When Ji Xiaolan came to Yunzhou
Lord Wu warmly welcomed him
Saying that the two of you have an extraordinary relationship
Lord Ji Juxiaolan was a scholar at the time
Officer, that was hospitality
It's not anything special
In fact, I have long hated Ji Xiaolan
But the emperor misunderstood himself
Mr. Wu, the color of your official cap feather is about to change
It's really unfair. Lord, your subordinate has been treated unjustly
But Lord Wu there is one way
to clear your name
Immediately drive Ji Xiaolan away
Don't leave this scourge anymore, understand?
the Emporer came
Come to Yunzhou without a word
what is he doing
Can't figure it out, can't figure it out
Ji Xiaolan, ah Ji Xiaolan
Where are you now the head of a scholar
Just a big pumpkin
There must be a reason
Where is Ji Xiaolan, where is Ji Xiaolan
Lord Wu, this wind and lightning
how come you're here
Listening to your voice, you're not here in friendship
Ji Xiaolan, I've seen you look evil for a long time
That's insincere, the emperor is wise and wise
You have been removed from office
what
People are now banned from the academy grounds without permission.
Someone threw his things out at me
This is a sage's book, you dare throw
goddamn you
Wuzui only judges people by wealth and power
God will punish you
That's my stuff, you give it back to me
Still the tiger skin belongs to me
Immediately report to Lord Heshen and Lord Fu Kangan
Just say I will take Ji Xiaolan
well repaired
Who dares to let him in the sedan
Stop the sedan for me
Look who is so bold
It's Lord He
Lord Heshen is you
I have kicked the surnamed Ji out of the academy
I even tore his umbrella
let him get soaked
Mr. Ji, come and come, my sedan chair is big
Squeeze the two of us and sit
come, come, Mr. Ji
Thanks, Lord Heshen, return my things
Mr. Ji come, have a drink with He Shen
come, please, please
Isn't this Lord Heshen and Ji Xiaolan mortal enemies?
Why did he come to help him?
I really don't understand
Mr. Ji works too hard, here
Warm up with a cup
This is the king's treasured wine
Lord Heshen brings such a good wine
hosting a newly dismissed employee
you must be asking for something
good wine
Ji Xiaolan is Ji Xiaolan
nothing can get past you
Lord Heshen, you've fed me now. What do you need?
sir please see
what is this
This is what I was about to ask you
Mr. Ji, who is famous all over the world, will surely know
Mr. Heshen, can I ask for advice?
where does this thing come from
This thing involves a major case in Beijing
it's the only line of inquiry
Sir please advise
This lock is called a longevity lock
worn by newborn babies
everywhere on the street
However
Fire's gone out
fire, come, light it
Just now you said
Lord Heshen this piece of gold
It is indeed different from other golden locks
Honestly, Mr. Ji said
I don't know how much I've seen this
I don't see anything special.
let go
There's nothing here
I'm knocking the ashes
Don't knock on this and you'll light it on fire
This lock is not special, thousands like it
But the goldsmiths who make locks
will leave a mark on themselves
mark
Did you see that there is a mountain spring?
This is a famous goldsmith in Yunzhou
Lin Xiaoquan's special mark
Mr. Ji, where does Lin Xiaoquan live now?
Now? I heard
This Lin Xiaoquan is now living in the Confucian Temple.
Thanks for Mr. Ji's information
come and drink
Mr. Ji all the way
Here
Ji Xiaolan, have a quick journey
Mr. Heshen, many thanks
let's go
goodbye
How come Ji Xiaolan, Lord Heshen, is leaving without a fuss
I got him out of a nice mess
Let him go back to Beijing to teach a few little babies to read
He just scuttled away
Lord Heshen is worthy of being the contemporary Confucious
Would not dare to be
But with Ji Xiaolan gone
We can really sit back and relax
But the gang of disaster victims are making trouble.
Let the adults help
don't worry about that
As long as we let the emperor look for his birth mother
He won't care about anything else
Lord He, let's go
He Aiqing, you are complex
Trivial, emporer doesn't need to mention it
I've been thinking about this golden lock day and night, but I didn't have any clues
Unexpectedly Heshen Aiqing
can actually find out about this Lin Xiaoxiaoquan
I am surprised
it's like this
Servant arrived in Yunzhou, day and night to check the darkness
Finally found Lin Xiaoquan's whereabouts
Then went to the cottage and asked questions
Only then did I notice the signature on the golden lock
I'm moved by He Aiqing's effort
You flatter me, the emperor is finding his mother
This filial piety makes the world feel moved
Heshen long decided
to help the emperor to uncover the truth of his life
He Shen, f I find my biological mother
you are the first to know
you flatter me, the emporer's most fortunate day
The slave is just shined a little light on it
The two masters are looking for Lin Xiaoquan
how do you know
Lin Xiaoquan is just waiting here
How did he know we were coming
He said you were for the golden lock
He is waiting for you at the Guandi Temple next to the Confucius Temple
This Lin Xiaoquan is simply a living sage
Master lead the way
two gentlemen
Lin Xiaoquan said that the two can only advance one
That's big talk does he knows we are?
Who does he want to see
He said which of the two of you is uglier
stays outside the door
Then you go in
Welcome your Majesty
Ji Xiaolan
Minister here, the emperor
Where is Lin Xiaoquan?
This Lin Xiaoquan was made up by the minister
you made it up
Then Heshen, he clearly told me
Only by using this method
Could Heshen lead you here
You and Heshen are bragging together
Ji Xiaolan
Do you know why I fired you?
please express, your Majesty
only after you became a commoner
did you help me with the secret investigation
your Majesty
I received a lot of  secret memos in the palace
Said that the food for disaster relief here
almost all of it was stolen
Up to the Governor and Governor down to Daofu Prefecture
collective corruption
I'm afraid this case is not easy to investigate.
I have already sent two batches of officials to investigate.
all in vain
A public inspection of such a case would be very effective
So, Your Majesty, you have to go undercover yourself
I realised when I arrived in Yunzhou
It's not that simple
It doesn't matter where I go
there are people who warn them first
I will never see the truth
That's when it's inconvenient to be the emperor
The same goes for being an official
If you are a political and local official, there is no reason not to flatter you
Food and wine plus beautiful women
but now you are a commoner it is much easier
You can definitely reveal the truth for me
The minister Ji Juxiaolan will never fail my emperor
In Ji Aiqing's opinion, where should one start?
The emperor should return to the capital immediately
Local officials can relax their vigilance
that will reveal all
I'll just do that. Heshen come in!
Emperor, Mr. Ji is also here
Heshen, where is Lin Xiaoquan?
Emporer, it's like this
I felt deeply that you could not let go of Ji Xiaolan
Therefore, this method is specially used to make the ruler and minister meet as soon as possible.
Hurry up and get your car back to the capital
Brother Huang, you are still not resting
yeah that ledger is missing
Write it down while my memory is still fresh
Officials protect each other, where can you go to sue you?
Unexpectedly, even Ji Xiaolan is so evil
Complain to the Imperial City
don't worry, you're afraid
I will accompany Brother Ming when going up to the Sword Mountain and down to the Sea of Fire
Who
I gonna go see
Brother Huang, officers and soldiers. flee
Mochou go quickly
freeze
Brother Huang
Mochou go quickly
Xiaoyue and the brothers can't be take care of themselves, go quickly
You go first!
If it doesn't work out
All the people in the disaster area have to starve to death, hurry up
Brother Huang
Why don't you listen to even my words?
He Shenqi. Enjoy
tell them to get out of the way
move apart
don't hurt them
they are my subordinates
Sister, why don't you let them go?
Take them all back
go up
I don't know enough, I really don't know enough
I didn't see such a little trick.
ashamed
natural calamities and man-made misfortunes are accidents
Aiqing, don't blame yourself
Ji Xiaolan, you are too presumptuous, this is for the emperor
Lord He, if you want to save the emperor
then I'm the only one who should sit here
Are you insane?
What's the matter with sitting or not sitting and getting out? Get up!
Ji Xiaolan
how do we get out
There are three possible ways for the emperor to escape
Number one
I sit and you stand
Number 2
Let Lord Heshen come and massage my back
in your dreams
Lord Heshen, you said
you would save the emperor even if you died
of course
Then why can't you massage my back?
what does this have to do with this
Of course
Heshen, do it...
I...
massage
work harder
Ji Xiaolan, the third point
The emperor pardon me
point three... I can't tell you for the time being.
Are you having fun?
you two bastards!
bastards!?
You are actually dared call us bastards
Not just bastards but losers
You've done me such a disservice
You are crazy, I will fight you
This scum official treats his subordinates
so poorly
He's really bad.
oh you've fallen
tell you as soon as I'm out
I'm going to banish you thousands of miles away
I'll let you never come back home
Crazy, this is crazy, I'll kill you
This is the third point
Ji Xiaoan you're locked away, and you still want to make threats
stand up
You two listen to me
No matter how long I'm stuck here
you have to also be stuck here
You, come and massage me
You, you have to pack me a cigar pot
Don't listen to the scum officer Xu Xian, come
We are all poor brothers
I'm on your side
scum officer won't try to bully you with me here
don't listen to her
You are not all the same
They're all locked up with me in this pile of stinky fish
who said they are locked here, I can let them go
You little girl, you have a big mouth
what are you capable of
If you want to let them go, you have to ask your boss's permission
you have no influence
let me tell you, we came today
just to get you scum officer
we had no intention of arresting your subordinates
It was my sister who asked me to come and see
if they are officials too
yes! they are also officials
You are arresting both was correct
you lying to me again!
No, he's the emporer!
He's the Minister of Defence and they're both higher rank than me
girl you arrested the right people
You think I'm a three year old
Both of them are higher rank than you?
He was massaging you just now
I saw it all outside the door
Girl I'm telling the truth
you must believe me
emperor?
Why am I not like the emperor?
Does the emperor look like you?
Look, you are a sturdy. You must lift the sedan chairs
a lifter? You really have a good eye
What about him? Does he look like a minister?
let's see
White and fat. he must sell tofu
nothing gets past you
Girl, what are you looking at?
shut up
I'm here today to fight for the poor brothers
you two come with me
what about him
stay. let's go
It's not fair. Your lord is sitting here
Your Lord is sitting here on the stinky fish
while you servants are free. You've put your foot in it now
Sister I've checked it out
two of them, one is a butler
one is a servant, neither of them are officials
Looking at your fancy clothes...
it's like this
We are working for the big family
gotta keep up the facade
In fact, inside and out
we only have one kind of these clothes
Sister, let them go, we're all suffering people
Besides, this Xu Xian also saved me.
ok let them go
Xu Xian, didn't I say
Our elder sister is the most concerned about the poor brothers
Thank you ma'am and thank you ma'am
Then let's go
wait
Take some silver taels and send them to two brothers
The two of you sit here for a while
Let you sit, just sit
sit
butler, servant
Yes, what's the matter
Have you ever seen a butler look after a servant?
butler serving servant
sister
Do you know how much this emerald finger is worth?
two buckets of fish
let them speak for themselves
I didn't expect you to be so stupid
what are you talking about
I was just dusting the chair
Respectfully asking the Holy Master to sit first
Who knew that woman was so tricky
You
You are so used to sucking up to the emperor
even when you shouldn't
OK, OK, OK
He said I was sucking up
How dare you three scum officials lie to me
Made me get told off by my older sister
I didn't lie to you, girl
I told you that the two of them are officials, you don't believe me
All three of you are no good
girl, let us three go
I'll ensure Huang Keming is okay and returns you wealth and glory
I won't be fooled by you, quick write
write what? to write a couplet?
Then my Ji Xiaolan's couplet is the best in the world
I'll do it
Who wants you to write some stupid couplets
Write a letter to Mr. Wu in Yunzhou Prefecture
Tell him to let brother Ming go
Otherwise, the three of you are dead
You see I said they were there to save Huang Keming
You are here to rescue Huang Keming
The one who just caught the court's scum officials?
You are so righteous
Girl, do you remember when you said
There is a actress who plays the white lady
You want to know her nickname again, right?
Yeah, what's her nickname?
want to know but I won't tell you
Don't listen to her, how does she know what nickname
she's bragging
Who doesn't know her nickname
Our sister said
I can't talk to you three scum officials. write quickly
Huang Keming, do you know what I'm here for?
come to kill me
Wrong, I'm here to tell you a story
I said how old are you
What are you tinkering with? It's fishy and smelly
You're not putting the emperor's safety first
Mr. Ji must be looking for something
of course the emperor knows me, emperor
what do you want
That half golden lock
I have never disclosed any rumors
You can guess that I have this item
You must have revealed it.
Servant wouldn't dare
Only you know my secret
if it wasn't you, who did?
The emperor's servant is guilty, servant is guilty and deserves death
okay, okay
The emperor and Lord He is not only innocent
You should also reward him
you don't have to speak for him
Lord Heshen holding the half of the golden lock
drew it as a picture and came to me
He didn't say it was the emperor's thing
but told me
it was some evidence in a case, right?
You could guess that it was mine
The emperor and Lord Shen have worked with ministers a lot
never asked a minister for help of his own affairs
he only has the interest of the emporer
He was willing to come to me and not be ashamed to ask
Then why did you come to ask me?
Since the emperor didn't tell me
It must be the emperor's secret
How could I dare to ask?
Then why do you dare to ask me now?
Your Majesty, we are now at the end of our lives.
Surely not, as long as the Yunzhou government releases Huang Keming
we'll be fine
The case of Huang Keming is now in the hands of Fukangan
Fukangan has a strong temperament and will not be threatened into obedience
He will not let Huang Keming go
then we're finished, all finished
He does't know the hostage is the emperor
Please look