barricade the opera house
don't let anyone go
so many palace soldiers
let me see
There really are a lot of soldiers
don't move
what are you doing
you Xiaoyue
Xiaoyue quickly take him into the wall
Walk
No wonder you dare to hide me here
you were already prepared
less talk, go inside
Xiaoyue
go fast
Sister, the dog official is hidden in the wall, you can relax
get out of the way
Sir, we only follow the rules and sing opera
Sir, we didn't find Mr Ji
impossible
I can see someone smoking a big pipe inside
really
The wall is empty, someone break it down for me
oh everyone came
The lord is really amazing
Sure enough, it's Ji Xiaolan
The troupe kidnapped an imperial official, arrest them
misunderstanding misunderstanding
Why does Fu Kangan talk about kidnapping?
Ji Xiaolan, didn't they kidnap you?
no such thing
I'm greedy for the troupe style
So I lingered
Look, this troupe are all acquaintances
They're all my good friends, right?
Sister, the dog official says we're good friend
Ji Xiaolan, you were locked in the wall
How do you explain that?
I have anxiety
It's a false alarm
dog official
Xiaoyue we can no longer call him dog official
Mr Ji saved us
you laugh and laugh
what?
how hard we tried to find you
Besides, why are you protecting the kidnappers?
Lord He, the master is not worried why are you?
you listen to this
Mr Ji must have his reasoning
Lord, look here
Lady Four walk quickly
This looks like Fu Kangan's soldiers
must be lively
go fast
We should not stay in the wrong place for a long time
If you don't enter a tiger's den, you can't get a tiger's son
Lady Four
Goddess of Mercy also has a golden lock
Master, you are an immortal who was born to meet the destiny.
who owns this painting
Wenzhen is a man
Asking you a question, are you dumb?
Lord
This painting is not our troupe's
Mr Ji what the hell is going on?
This painting is hanging here
I don't know what's going on
Who's is this
yeah not yours
How to explain this painting
I don't know
Who's is this
please don't implicate us all
I am here thank you
Lord, don't get agitated
Let's take them back and interrogate them
We'll definitely get to the bottom of it
yes, take everyone back
My God, who bought it, who hung it up?
Hurry up and talk, my mother
Take them all back to the government office
Wait, Mr Ji must have an explanation, right?
I can probably guess who's this picture is
Du Xiaoyue own up to what you did
I
take her
You dog official dare to lie
Master, can you let me interrogate her in private?
you
Mr Ji of course
Thank you Master
let's go
let me tell you, I painted that painting
dog official you want to harm us
Xiaoyue listen to what he has to say
I remember
last afternoon you were by the painting
painted a whole afternoon
go tell them the truth
Xiaoyue
Mr Ji wouldn't paint for no reason
I think you have your intentions, right?
yes Mochou is smart
I ask you whether the ledger is important or not
If you have the ledger, you can sue Yancheng officials.
Rescue the victims
Okay, then your brother Huang Keming had the ledger.
Why couldn't he sue the government?
Officials protect each other
to sue the government
Not only must there be evidence, but also a plan
what plan
The painting is the plan
painting?
Please explain
no time now
Anyway, when we go
Whatever I say, just say yes
Also be sure to remember
Lord Heshen, I think Ji Xiaolan has
a secret with them
You can't say this in front of your master.
If there is no conspiracy, why are they being sneaky?
Ji Xiaolan helped the master find this painting
A great achievement
your illustrious feats
cannot compare to his
Literati dogs, despicable
How is it, Mr Ji?
Du Xiaoyue, explain it yourself
Miss Xiaoyue's painting looks broken
did you buy it
You are right, it was given to me by my master
your master
oh no
opera teacher
where is your master now
Do you want to know? You have to agree to my conditions first
Presumptuous
Say
First of all, don't bother this opera troupe anymore
I promise
good
The second is to restore the name of Huang Keming, brother Huang
no reason
I also promise this one
third
third third third
If there is no third, don't make random conditions
third
About Mr Ji
Of course, about our kidnapping of Mr Ji
you won't hold us accountable
If Mr Ji doesn't care, why should I pursue it
so refreshing
Are these three conditions taught by you?
I can't hide anything from the eyes of Lord Heshen
Xiaoyue, what is your master's name
My master's surname is Bai
white?
self-proclaimed the white lady
the white lady
where does she live
Yancheng
Lord, Qianlong is going to Yancheng
Lady Four was originally a liar
what
Qianlong was originally Yongzheng's biological son
Where folktale come from about his birth mother?
What about the golden lock and the white lady?
I have never heard Yongzheng talk about it
Royal Lord, let's go to Yancheng too
what?
Qianlong looks for his mother in his commoner clothes
There are definitely not many people with him
If you and I rushed to Yancheng and we can kill him
unknown to god or ghost
Lady Four
This is a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity
This is Lord Kangxi giving you a chance in the dark, Lord
I don't want to be emperor
But I want to be Queen
Lord Heshen, can't you stop the emperor?
Brother, you don't know the Lord
What kind of place is Yancheng
How can the master take risks so easily?
But the master is the most filial person
Once he learned of his birth mother
How can he sit still?
can you not dissuade the emperor
the position of top minister is wasted
Brother is right
Then tomorrow morning I will face the holy death remonstrance
Sir, this is absolutely impossible
under the right words
If the emperor really does not listen to the advice
I will kill myself on the spot
Sir, I will accompany you
good
There is a woman calling herself Du Xiaoyue who wants to visit
Du Xiaoyue, an opera singer, I don't want to see her
My lord Du Xiaoyue said she came to deliver a letter
whose letter
Xu Shan
absurd, chuck her out
let her, let's invite her in
Sir this
please come in please come in
what don't you know me anymore
Xiaoyue, Xu Xian's letter?
Yes
Did he say who it's for?
he said just give this letter to a fat man
The fat man looks like it's for me
How come it's for you?
Sir, look around, I'm the fat one
Is it, Wu Zhifu?
You can know the allusion to referring to a deer as a horse
Lord Fu, look at me compared to Wu Zhifu
who is fatter
Of course, Lord Heshen is fat
you see
Of course, of course, Mr. Heshen
You see that your heaven is full
Face is round and red, full of great fortune
It's okay, Wu Zui has to be a bit more subtle with flattery
Great fortuen can only be said to be the emperor
I'm just a little fatter than you
more than a bit fat
Look how thin Wu is now
You are smart
Miss Xiaoyue gave me the letter
it was for you
What does the emperor say
The emperor said let us three
Give their official seals to Xiaoyue
what does the emperor mean
He said he was going to play
What's so funny about the official seal?
I don't know at the moment
Master's word is what it is
hey hurry up
Xu Xian said there was stuff for me to bring back
Right, Xu Xian also said
that you will take me back in a sedan chair
Master Wu, then prepare the sedan chair
Send Xiaoyue back
they're really heavy
come come put them here
Mr Ji, the official seals you wanted
I got them all for you
good seals really good seals
But I still don't understand
What do you want these official seals for?
With these official seals
I can find out what you asked me to investigate.
It's that simple
Then Mr Ji's plan
I have to guess
Xiaoyue, do you have a seal in your troupe?
seal, we have
bring one over here
Why didn't Lord Heshen enter to dissuade the emperor?
I came at dawn
But the emperor sent guards, no one was allowed to enter
Not even Lord Heshen
After how many years, this is the first time
It's because of Ji Xiaolan
enter
Lord Fu, what are you doing?
The emperor doesn't let us enter
I also don't let the emperor go to Yancheng
This is absolutely impossible
You are just crazy
Lord Heshen, in order to protect the emperor
I, Kangan will not rest until dead
Such strong resolve in this loyal minister
Today, He Shen sees you
Can the Emperor see us?
the emperor left at midnight
and you only just opened the door
You didn't mean to tease us, did you?
Don't get me wrong, two Lords
The emperor gave me orders
Only open the door at the end of the day
Otherwise, I would be punished with treason
This must be Ji Xiaolan's top idea
Heshen, let's chase
The two adults must stay in Yunzhou and cannot leave without permission
Walk
slow, stop
Mochou let's wait for him here
where are you from
we come from Yancheng
Yancheng has a large amount of food for disaster relief
They were all shipped from Lotau's warehouse.
official's are cruel
We get a grain
Mr Ji, you and Fu Kangan
are both big palace officials
All respect him
Who is this Xu Xian?
I cannot say
willing to brave the heat
to find his birth mother
This man must not be bad
well said
But once we get to Yancheng
and he doesn't find his biological mother
What to do when he arrives
After arriving at Yancheng, I'm afraid I can't help him
Xu Xian, don't look, you can't save them
Xiaoyue, make speed ​​to Yancheng
Mr Ji now I understand
Why you want to take me to Yancheng
hey go
I'm so restless, and you can calmly drink tea
What's the use of urgency, brother
I can't taste the real taste in a hurry
Ji Xiaolan led the emperor to Yancheng
Obviously not looking for the emperor's biological mother
But to thoroughly investigate the case of stolen grain relief.
OK bro
It seems that Ji Xiaolan's move
didn't get past you
But Ji Xiaolan took the emperor by the nose to Yancheng
we cannot keep a handle on the case
So we have to rush to Yancheng
to stop this
But the emperor has ordered
You and I can't move
I want to go to Yancheng
certainly
easy to handle
find him
News from the government office
Qianlong went to Yancheng in the middle of the night
Sir, why don't you speak
don't mention it again
Fu Kangan is already within my grasp
Using him, we can get to Qianlong
Take advantage of the opportunity
Lady Four I want to go back to the capital
Lord
I want you to go with me
Fourteenth Lord
Just lead him to Yancheng
we can then
Justifiably rush to Yancheng
Why would he go to Yancheng?
He's going to assassinate the emperor
And we are going to the rescue
But the Fourteenth Lord is now a bird in shock
He never dared to leave Yunzhou for half a step.
That time is over
Besides, you and Lady Four are courting
can't you impress her
Lady Four
Why do adults impound my car?
let me go
Why would you impound my car and let me go?
Xiaoyue, listen to me
You have to be calm and not impulsive
No matter what happens, you can't attack
Do you understand?
I get it, you said it 800 times
old people talk too much
Too much talk, Mr. Ji, let's go
Hey, stop those people for me
what you doing
Ordered to track down the anti-Qing and Fuming rebels
we are merchants
can't you tell?
merchents?
Anti-Qing Fu Ming rebels
are all pretending to be merchants
I see you look
Just like the anti-Qing and Fu Ming rebels
me, rebel?
I say this soldier, you have a sharp eye
detain them for me
you dare
Mr Ji, maybe they just want a bribe
Oh I have it
This man, we are really merchants
ah merchants
As soon as I see you, I think you are honest businessmen
Yes Yes Yes
off you go
thank you sir thank you
Which office are you with, what is your name?
yeah, which office
paying your respects eh
Thank you, sir, thank you
go, go, go, go
Come over, are you hiding something?
Is there anything good hidden in you?
you look pretty
don't let a small thing turn into a big mess
let's go
It's important to find the white lady
search her for me
let me go
Girl, don't be afraid, I'm here
Xu Xian, nice going
Shame on your face, you are courting death
girl you go first
You are shaming the whole Qing Dynasty
catch this guy, attack
What should we do, Mr Ji?
What else is there to do? Attack
Xiaoyue take them fast
why are you laughing
I laugh so loudly the emperor of the Qing Dynasty
Fighting with people like a street prankster
i forget it happened
The imperial throne's purpose cannot be forgotten
I remember the words of good sir
stop, I'll see where you run to
what are you doing
Lord, you forgot your purpose again
I'm happy
I'm in trouble if you're happy
here, here, hurry up, here
what are you doing
There are bad people chasing us, help
Hurry, hurry in, hurry in, hurry in
go this way
Grab them and tear them limb from limb, search!
what to do
hide first
search carefully
get out the way
Your Majesty, look at this basket there are six long lines
This is the hexagram of Qian
Qiangua, flying dragon
What's the matter
what to do, sister
we are surrounded
Where did the flying dragon sign come from?
Strange, this sign can't be wrong.
we're going to become pincushions
Your Majesty, this is obviously the hexagram of Qian
flying dragon in the sky
The emperor is flying dragon
Sir, you are a sage
I'm not a sage
I just read a lot
Your Majesty, look at the flying dragon in the sky
Catch the two criminals
Sister, the dog soldiers come up
Sir do you have a solution
Many problems, no solutions
They must be hiding in there and stab him at me
Mr Ji go
careful
Xu Xian, nice
The inner heroine, admirable
no time to admire, let's go
Mr Ji, please help
Okay, who am I here to help?
help her
I see
don't delay, go
OK
Xiaoyue go with them quickly
chase after her
Lord
to go or not to go
The carriage is ready
Lady Four, are you willing to go to Beijing with me?
Four is with the Lord for life
Where Lord goes I go?
You don't have to for a criminal
Ruin your great youth
I have no regrets
Lady Four I can't make you queen
Lord is indifferent to fame and fortune, Four admires it
You know me like my father Lord Kangxi knew me
Royal Lord
Let's go
I think we'll stay here
We also stay in the inn
I can't let you, Xu Xian, live on the high street.
Mr Ji
there are people chasing us everywhere
they will definitely come to check on this inn
i thought about it
He'll look up four single men and women
But he won't check for two married couples
Where are two married couples
isn't this two married couples
The two of them are not husband and wife
let's go
If the two of them are a couple, what about us?
we are also a married couple
you wish! I don't want to be paired with you
Xiaoyue, after we go in
pretend not to recognise them
definitely don't say hi to them
I don't want to pretend to be husband and wife
If I wanted to pretend, I'd pretend with Xu Xian
why
he more handsome than you
Walk
please enter
Are you satisfied?
Not bad, it will do
here waiter, a tip
thank you sir, lady
call me if you need something
go Go
lock the door
huh, surnamed Ji, you really eat a leopard's guts
I didn't eat
The thief is immortal and courageous again
Xiaoyue you are
don't think to take advantage of me
You know how good my martial arts are
I'll explain to you, okay?
There is someone here, so don't reveal it
someone meter
who
the waiter, bringing water
come in
Mr and Mrs, hot water
who is his wife
come on wife
I really didn't peek at that girl just now
Although she is beautiful
But I didn't even look at her
waiter, find me a room, I want to move out
Madam, the gentleman looking at other women
isn't with emotions
don't take it too seriously
What did you say
madam i admit i did see her
I said a few words to her
I touched her hand too
Second, I'm not a husband at all with him.
it's that he rather die than lose face
I know
what do you know?
Lord, messing around outside
Madam, you have to teach him a lesson, he deserves it
waiter you are really smart
Stupid, look at me like this
do I look  like his wife
yes you do
how?
It's not obvious
It's all kindness and love that come out after cheating
as angry as you madam
Must the first wife
You are so smart, you said it well
Come on, sir, I'll give another tup
not allowed
madam won't let me give
she's angry
Sir, you can do it yourself
Thanks for reminding
stupid you piss me off
I just won't sleep tonight
I can't be here either, I'm leaving
madam madam can't go
Xiaoyue, do you want to avenge Huang Keming?
Do you want to help the people in the disaster area?
of course, even in my dreams
Then you have to pretend to be husband and wife with me tonight
who are you deceiving
if i guess right
It will be known tonight
tonight
right
Then we won't have to pretend to be husband and wife tomorrow.
Tomorrow you can pretend to be my mother
am i that old
Xu Xian, go to bed
i sit here all night
Mochou have you ever thought about it
Why does Ji Xiaolan and Xiaoyue pretend to be husband and wife?
but pushed you to me
I don't know
If Xiaoyue lives with me
In less than a night, you will be asked left and right by me
She would not be able to keep her secret
This was painted by Xiaoyue's Master
If this picture is really Xiaoyue's
Ji Yun would have let her stay with me
and let me ask her carefully
and inquire about her master's whereabouts
He pushed you to me first
That's more of a disguise
I'm starting to doubt the authenticity of this painting
Xu Xian
The painting didn't fall
As if the painter was afraid that others would recognize him
Ink is still new
It's lnot ike what Xiaoyue's master would leave behind
Ji Xiaolan painted it, right?
you
this is your fan
Mochou look at this fan
This is pen and ink
Doesn't this and the painting
share many similarities
This fan was painted by Ji Xiaolan
He thought because he didn't sign it, I wouldn't recognise it
Unexpectedly his talent showed him
Xu Xian, you also leaked your secret
I
This fan is written with minister Ji Yun
your Majesty your Majesty
Mochou I don't need to be polite for private patrols
You still call me Xu Xian
Emperor, no, Xu Xian
The people in the disaster area are looking forward to your visit
i came too late
Lord
Who would dare to leave the Fourteenth Lord here?
Fourteenth Lord shall not leave
who is so bold
emperor
The imperial decree is a greater than a mountain, asking the Fourteenth Lordto come back
Sir, have you seen it?
Qianlong has rules for you
You are still under house arrest here
What is the difference between this and Yongzheng?
Lady Four be careful
I'm not afraid, kill me if you dare
no nonsense, let's return
Fourteenth Lord?
Yes, I have come to Yancheng
There must be someone who will take advantage of the fourteenth Lord
make trouble
So I have ordered that
It is strictly forbidden for Lord Fourteen Ren to leave the cloud
I'm afraid your Majesty's effort
the Fourteenth Lord won't appreciate
Whether he appreciates or not I don't care
Since my enthronement
Every policy implemented
Which one is has not faced
Criticism of the old ministers in the capital
Which order has been implemented smoothly
I never imagined it would be so difficult to be emperor
If there is even one corrupt official in the world
it is the emperor's fault
In the world there are people suffering
that is the failure of the emperor
The Son of Heaven The Son of Heaven
how can one not be frightened and trembling with fear?
you are not resting
After I left the capital
have ordered them to bring all the throne's memos
Send it to Yunzhou with a fast horse
There must be no negligence
no movement at all
maybe they were fed up of your overacting?
oh, don't worry
hey yes
In a moment I'll throw some stuff down
you scold me loudly
scold, I can't
Oh, what's wrong with scolding people?
you scold me
scold you for no reason
I can't scold
oh, which one has no eyes
are your eyes on your behind?
wife, wife
how come you are throwing my stuff out
waiter, have you seen my stuff?
Yo, it's you
tigress at home
sorry
ouch lady wife
You can't throw this thing away
Madam, this thing can't be thrown away
Ouch, can't stay here
you're crazy
If the inn asks you to pay later
you will be screwed
Don't worry, they not only won't let me pay
they will send a new ones
wife, please have mercy
This can't be thrown anymore
Let's make it clear
It's none of my business, pay for it yourself
hey wife, wife
Oh wife, you have no mercy
such a large seal
This print is reversed. Bring a piece of paper.
Who's is this seal?
Minister of defence Heshen