Sirs, your tea is here
This tea is very good
How are you, Uncle Fourteen?
buy hot buns
Buns
I warn you if you try to run
I'll not be so kind to you
What's this, wonton?
Madam what are you selling?
Wontons I have to eat bowls of wontons
Xiaoyue, please sit with me, I'll pay
I'm not eating, you hurry up
If my sister knew that I took you out, she would scold me to death
It's  because you bring me to such a good place
that I'll repay you after I'm full
by immediately write down the ledger for you
Really, then you eat more
The lady boss add another bowl
Don't don't don't, what place is this?
Lord Heshen, this Lord Fourteen
How can I bring my master here for dinner?
Relax, the master won't eat here
Well, let's have a late night supper here
Master here, the dragons and snakes are mixed and the safety is worrying.
Heshen, you and Kang An...
I'm still
I want to talk to Uncle Fourteen
what do we do?
Uncle Fourteen has been in Yunzhou for many years, you pick the food
They all know what I want to eat
good
the usual
got it
Why doesn't the emperor let them sit at the same table?
I have some family matters that I want to ask Fourteen
Has Uncle Fourteen ever seen this golden lock?
This golden lock looks familiar
lay it down
I want this golden lock
Leave it to the master at this time
Besides, with the master's skill
More than enough to deal with these gangsters
Uncle Fourteen let the man bring the wine
you guys have help
Where did this golden lock come from?
Nanny
Why are you like a starving ghost reincarnated?
you made me miss many meals
Moreover
The taste here is not the same in the capital
so i should eat more bowls
what?
Fukangan
don't move
What are you doing, Xiaoyue
I know what's on your mind
what am I thinking?
When you see Fu Kangan, you want to ask him for help
Take the opportunity to escape, right?
Xiaoyue, I really respect you
You are really a Lady Confucious, take it easy
As if it needed to be said
go!
thank you for the rescue, lady
Why do you have to be polite, please sit down
ok
Ah youth
flirting at first sight
Oh no, that fat guy is here too
he came too
I'm so stupid I shouldn't have told him
You are afraid of me running away
go you can't eat anymore
Xiaoyue
Let's take two more buns back
No, it would be troublesome for them to see
that's what would be stupid
You think we sat for a long time and they didn't see
As soon as we get up, they'll see
sit back down
Turn your face around
buy a flute, buy a flute
I buy a flute from the flute seller
what are you doing
You see this old man is still selling flutes so late
What a pity, buy one
thanks
Isn't this the tune of the Legend of the White Snake?
you can play it too
The nanny was seriously ill and may have been delirious
The emperor cannot trust her
Nanny's dying words shouldn't deceive me
This can only be opened if the locksmith is found
I've seen this golden lock
Uncle Fourteen, where?
I think is was...
Uncle Fourteen, you must think
It's about my life
How many winds and winds over the years
Uncle Fourteen
years ago
I have seen such golden locks in Yunzhou City
It seems to be in the Laojun Temple in the south of the city.
There is such a gold shop
yes must be there
Gold shop near Laojun Temple
right
Master, did you here?
This is the ancient music of Ouchi offering sacrifice to heaven
Who in the land of Yunzhou can play this song
Yes, could it be Ji Xiaolan?
Lord above, it's possible, I will go to see
good
This is not the legend of the White Snake
Is it the tune of your hometown?
yeah you're so smart
very nice
It's Ji Xiaolan
you lured him here!
do not move
I don't move, you don't either
Thank goodness you came
Otherwise I will have
had to deal with the two of them
Who told you to bring the dog officer outside, bring him here
go, he said he was hungry
How did I know he was scheming
lady, take me alone
Yeah, I'm absolutely useless
no use at all
still up
Huang Keming's blood debt
You two can't add up.
where to go
This way
Sister, they are all here
Let them go, I won't let you get away
Water, water, I can't swim, I really can't swim
Can't swim, perfect, go in!
Sister, he really doesn't know how to swim
we go down
Lord, we should not stay for a long time, go quickly
you see
We are surrounded with water, what do we do?
Just because we can't swim
They are relieved
to lock us up on this island
stop smoking
Can't even smoke anyway
The tobacco is all wet, how can I live like this
you two dogs
Weren't you escaping, I'd like to see you try
Xiaoyue, is this fish is for me
In your dreams
Such a shame, I only had one bite of that yellow fish
Wouldn't you say it's regretful
At this point in time
You're only thinking about your fish, this guy is so boring
I don't have tabacco to smoke, I don't have fish to eat, it's...
Lord Heshen, how can we get out?
You ask me, I want to ask you
Ji Xiaolan, who is also the number one scholar in the world
Can't think of an escape plan
I have been thinking this whole time
But she locked us in such a water island
Not even a sage would have a plan
Not really, you can ask her
ask who
I see that girl treats you well
Mr. Heshen, Xiaoyue
Think of a way out for us to escape, please?
Of course there is a way to escape
Just jump in the water and swim out.
Now it's up to you two to spend time making fish couplets
You have nowhere to run
Making fish couplets, against who? I don't have a worthy opponent
May I ask Mr. Ji what book references the five-color fish?
Notes on the Classic of Water
half-faced fish
Reference
Kuaji Chronicle
Heshen, which book references the concubine fish?
The fish with the elegant sword
Su Dongpo's Poetry and the Fish of the Team
Poems of Han Yu
No, Mr. Heshen
How's is it wrong?
Young and long gatherings are different from the same team of fish
It's obviously Han Yu's poems from the South of the Reading City
I mean the three of us
In the fish warehouse, were making fish couplets
The ones you said were the most illiterate
It's not just vulgar, it's just crap
What snake oil are you selling?
You obviously have a wealth of knowledge in that belly
Mr. Ji your intellect level is league above me
On being a government official, you are league below
What does Mr. Heshen mean by this?
Why would I steal the limelight with the emperor present?
It's not like you don't know
The emperor is known as the First Ancient Scholar
Only fools show off intellectually in front of him
I'm so stupid
So after so many years
Although Mr. Ji is quite appreciated by the emperor
Rarely gets promoted
I think that's probably the reason, isn't it?
Mr. Ji, I always think
If we can join forces
Isn't that a grand plan?
What Mr. Heshen means
Divide the two evils and combine the two benefits
Hope you figure it out next time we meet
Next time we meet, you're leaving?
Of course, I'm going first, I'm afraid I'm  not accompany you
Yeah right, you're going first
we are stuck on this island
There is water all around, where are you going?
I know
No way, Mr. Heshen
You can swim
Of course I can swim
How did Mr. Ji forget?
Where did He Shen get promoted from, the Imperial Guard
We fight tigers in the mountains and dragons in water
So when Xiaoyue pushed you into the water
You shouted that I can't swim, I can't swim
If I don't shout like that
Would they take us to this island?
And send only this girl to guard. Excellent
Lord Heshen is really brilliant
I'm the only one who's stupid, I really can't swim
Lord Heshen, then let me tag along, let's go.
I'm so sorry Mr. Ji
I really want to take you
let's go then
But the heart is not
Heshen's swimming power is not enough to take Mr. Ji
So, Mr. Ji, please be safe
you sit here, sit here
can't take me
No, no, no, really sit here, sit here
But you relax
I will inform the emperor as soon as possible
We'll send people to rescue you
Besides, if the two of us are together
She will see no one here
think about it
I'm sure Mr. Ji will realise the importance of the overall situation
let's go
tell the emperor
pyrene
I written Huang Keming's ledger in my heart
They won't be able to kill me for a while
you mean
you mean you have memorized all of Huang Keming's ledger
Yes, go then
Mr. Ji has a good memory
move
Okay, I'm going
I'm so stupid
Lord, why did you save Qianlong instead?
I can't not help
This kind of thought, you will regret for life
He is my relative
How could I endure watching him die
Did Yongzheng treat you as a relative
Qianlong is my nephew, I held him when he was a child
Lord, there is a lot of importance on the half piece of golden lock
great importance
As long as Qianlong is a Han person
He is not qualified to be the Emperor
But there are many rumors about this, but there is no evidence
The proof is is your hands
in my hands
You are his uncle, what you say is proof
But we don't know anything
When Yongzheng died, you  became his only elder
What you say counts
If you say he is a Han, then he is a Han
Lady Four
This is the fatal blow to Qianlong
what is this
This is the emblem of Lord Fourteen
Emblem of the Lord Fourteen
No wonder he wants to take the emperor to the wharf for a late night snack
It turns out that he had already arranged an assassin.
What do you think Heshen
Servant sees that if the Lord Fourteen wants to assassinate the emperor
why would he use his own people
Just buy a batch of outlaws to do the job
tattoos left on corpse
This would give him away
Heshen Aiqing is right
but it's obviously...
Fukangan, you are just too impulsive
In the future, I have to learn more from Lord Heshen
Yes
Wu Zui
minister here
Fourteenth Lord said
There is a goldsmith around Laojun Temple in the south of the city
i want to see
You go to inquire first, then quickly return
Lord He
Obviously you asked someone to tattoo the corpse
but you then
brother, listen to me
On the contrary, you vouched for the Fourteenth Lord
We can't get someone killed over a tattoo
Nothing in the world is so easy
But isn't that what you said to do?
How smart is the emperor
How could he be deceived by such obvious evidence planting
but that tattoo
That tattoo is like an ant gnawing a dike
Today one bite, tomorrow another
Can't stand for a long time
after a long time even the longest embankment will burst
But I still don't understand
There's one thing you must know, brother, let me ask
Who is our biggest belly trouble?
Fourteenth Lord
No he's just a underdog
But who else dares to oppose us except him
Ji Xiaolan
Ji Xiaolan, just a scholar
you should not underestimate him
Take Huang Keming's ledger as an example.
I thought it was burnt, no more problem
who would have thought
He actually memorized the entire ledger.
Lord, we must not let him come back
Yeah, but with his ability
He'll be back, I can't stop it
What do we do, sir
There is a way
We can't stop him, we can let the emperor go first
The emperor is in a hurry to find the gold shop
Why would he leave
It is just that goldsmith
that will be enough to make the emperor return to the capital early
But I still don't understand
Come on brother, let me tell you slowly
How are you guarding people
Even on this small island, you let people escape
He clearly said he can't swim, liar
Mochou
You really can't blame this Xiaoyue
Even I was deceived by that fat dog officer
If you see that fat dog in the future, you must be careful
Don't be like me, simple and honest
you can relax with me
You can also play the flute in return for leaning on you, and you are cunning enough
we already discussed it
I write out the ledger and you let me go
Why do I have to run away?
You haven't written the ledger yet
Don't blame me, I'm dizzy with hunger
How can I write it?
What he said is quite reasonable.
Shut up for me, we can't stay in this place long
Xiaoyue take him to the dock
With all due respect, you must not go to this dock
I said we go so we go
If you are more wordy, I will be punish you
Sister Mochou Mochou
what happened?
Officers and soldiers are searching the dock
So many people, that scene is horrible
This shredded tobacco is dry now, life is worth living
Ma'am, he's so smart
Thankfully we didn't go there
Once they cast the net
Not a single fish, shrimp, crab can escape
how did you know
Mochou
You locked the three of us in a fish warehouse
Later, they hijacked the fat man at the dock.
Locking us up on this island again
Not all officers and soldiers are stupid.
Sooner or later they would search the dock
It makes sense, the dog officer is not dumb
Where else can we hide people?
only the opera troupe
The troupe is not good, the government just searched it
Miss Mochou, they searched the troupes once
they would not again
Dog official is a smart dog
Xiaoyue take him away
go, did you hear? go
Lord Wu we did not find the gold shop
There are no gold shops in this area
Didn't the emperor say that there is gold shop
There were some a few years ago but now they are closed
close down
what do we do?
What do you mean
the gold shop
there is a gold shop here
Where is the gold shop?
Mr. Wu, you can't see
Forgive me, if i cannot see
Isn't the gold shop right here?
Lord Wu, if you want to keep your rank
There must be a gold shop in this area
But the subordinate has been looking all day
it is good
I only give you one day
If after one day
there is no gold shop here
you go home and grow sweet potatoes
Of course, there is a gold shop, there is a gold shop Heshen
Your eyes are darting around, you want to run away
As soon as I run away, the sword in your hand won't last long
Good that you know
I always thought was strange
I'm a stranger walking around backstage
why has no one asked me anything
Everyone knows Brother Huang, who isn't helping us
Huang Keming is alive in people's heart
Xiaoyue bring me some ink
You wish I bring it to you
I have to write down Huang Keming's ledger
In honour of Huang Keming's spirit
Dog officer, you are no so bad
If it's not bad, then don't call the dog official
come come come, good dog, write quicklys
Why are you still calling me dog?
Shen Hao, the prefect of Yunzhou, sells the Chaoguan disaster food to the victims
100 taels of silver
Xiaoyue, here
You write and I read it, it will be faster
I can't write
Come and look
Look at these two words, what are they?
what is this
this is your name
my name is like this
yes, Xiaoyue
Xiaoyue
you have to learn to write your name
Come and let me teach you to write and sit
No, no, no, I hold a pen heavier than a sword
How can a warrior not write?
come come write write
right
don't press so hard
go down, go down and flick
you see
I'll hold the top
don't go against me, try to follow me
what do you thnk
Xiaoyue, I can write my own name
Yep
This is the place, master
Heshen, look at the signboard, this golden lock
Exactly the same, congratulations on finding it, master
Yes I made it
Do you remember the name of the person who ordered the golden lock?
decades ago
I don't know if the customer's name can still be found
Don't worry, find it slowly
Found the one who ordered this golden lock
It's a young man who claims to be from the capital
From the Capital, what's the name
Shi Beile
Shi Beile never heard this person's name
Lord please see
This is written on the fifteenth day of the eighth month
Shi Beile, ordered the golden lock of longevity
I wish all the elders and wives could be together in a thousand miles
What kind of man was Shi Beile
Shi Beile, royal father!
yes lord
Look again at the words "Thousand Miles Together"
It was clearly written by the late Emperor Yongzheng
Yeah, it's very similar
This is the stuff of the ancestors
It can be seen that the master is indeed the real son of the late emperor
This half piece of golden lock is iron proof
Congratulations, you are a real banner man
Dragon Blood Dragon Vein of Destiny
What do you think?
Not bad, some are fat and some are thin
San'er
coming
Post this sign on the stand in the garden
Which play are we playing tonight?
Wangjiang Pavilion
Good show, I'm famous for playing Tan Ji'er
really?
Yup
It's a pity that Mochou won't let you on stage
With the hree words, Du Xiaoyue
we'd sell out the theatre
I'll just help out backstage
This sign doesn't look like a great opera troupe's
The troupe people are like me
they are lucky to be able to write two words
Hanging out such a sign will embarrass the troupe
Xiaoyue, this big brother can write
Can you
Of course, for the big opera troupe in the Capital
I write everything, whether it's Jin Liansheng...
He Shenchun Pavilion Celebration Class. All written by me
Then you also help us write one
I can't write now I'm a prisoner
Knowing that you are prisoner, you should cooperate, are you going to write it?
Well, I write, I write, you see, I write
Xiaoyue, female warrior
The dog officer is afraid of fighting. Only my fists can persuade him
Master, it's time we go back to the capital
The origin of the golden lock has been identified
The identity of the master is clear
No need to stay in Yunzhou anymore
But Ji Xiaolan was not yet rescued
I am uneasy
Lord, don't worry
I will definitely rescue Ji Xiaolan
Yunzhou is not a safe place and you cannot stay for a long time
Yeah and the Fourteenth Lord
is also suspicious
The emperor should return to Capital early
You two are singing the same tune together
Intentionally not letting me stay in Yunzhou
Not at all
Master leads the country
China's big affairs are all waiting for you to handle
Each day the master stays, the world is uneasy
Fukangan, you dare to contradict me
Do you want to be like Nian Genyao (traitor)?
Lord, please calm down, please calm down
Fukang An is loyal and commendable
How could he be Nian Genyao?
After all, Master is not Emperor Yongzheng
I ask the master to forgive his rudeness
Nian Genyao
you go down
Get in the car, you two
master
Get in the car
You two are not allowed to peep, if you do you'll be punished
Eunuch Wang, last time you said that the emperor was driving in the street
Everyone thinks you're a laughing stock
what i said is true
The emperor, it really is the emperor, you see
where is where
on the horse carriage
is his emperor
It's the driver again
That's right, the emperor
You think the emperor is so bored with nothing to do
that comes here every day to drive a horse carriage
I'm telling the truth
girl, we have a problem
Are we not playing the Wangjiang Pavilion?
How can it be changed to Legend of the White Snake?
you wrote the white snake
You see, I keep thinking about eating snakes
I just accidentally wrote the legend of the White Snake
Master, then change the sign
It's too late. Today, it's all the government offices.
Hurry up and find someone to play the white lady
You see, you see, this troupe leader is really good
Just like that they can change the play
Dog officer is this your trick?
Change the play and they will come
who will come who will come
giving you a full house
If you don't believe it, you must see it
so many people
So because today is full
Don't forget to ask the leader to treat me to eat snake
you wish
don't recognise it?
This is what you two brought me
Dafa Gold Shop
down
Where is the gold shop and where is the old goldsmith?
Where is the account book written by the emperor?
Is this gold shop fake?
servant be damned
Do you know how I saw the flaw?
servant does not know
using the account book, using the emperor
It was written that I hope people grow up a thousand miles together.
Remember the story of the late emperor killing Nian Gengyao?
I know a little
On the eve of Emperor Yongzheng killing Nianyingyao
he wrote these two words as a warning
But why did Lord Yongzheng write these two sentences?
For your son
The emperor's eyes are like torches and servant throws himself to the ground in admiration
Fukangan
You came up with this ruse didn't you?
Yes, this was just me
Nothing to do with Lord He
No this idea is was mine
how dare you?
How dare you deceive me
Your Majesty, in order to find the Golden Lock
Endangered the state of the government
servant's heart was restless
Emperor, if you really find out that you are Han Chinese
That is the biggest crisis of the Qing Dynasty
Therefore, servant set up hypotheses and perjury
Hoping that the emperor could return to the Capital
This is the blessing of the Qing Dynasty and the blessing of all the people
Long live the safety of the Qing Dynasty
Kang An can't sit idly by
The emperor's servant deceived you
It's a crime that deserves death
Servant is willing to accompany Lord Heshen to death
Break the corpse into pieces without complaint
But please go back to the Capital quickly
May the blood of us servants wake up the emperor
The servants can die contently
emperor
get up, get up, get up
You are all loyal, how can I not understand
Thanks, Emperor
I'm restless, you two walk with me
Heshen will leave tomorrow morning and I will return to the Capital
Master you must be tired
why don't you go back sooner to reset
yes
Ji Xiaolan hasn't come back, I can't relax
The master doesn't have to worry
You see Ji Xiaolan's face that is blessed
It's sure to be a blessing in disguise
there's a play on
I met Du Xiaoyue at this theatre
Master, do you want to watch the show to relieve boredom?
not in the mood, I'm returning
Then servant will prepare the sedan chair
Today's role in The Legend of the White Snake is not bad
Master, they talk about the legend of the White Snake
Let's see who will play the white lady
master, this is not Du Xiaoyue
It's Hua Yanfang
look at those words
is it mispelled?
This is Ji Xiaolan's handwriting
sung really well
Xiaoyue let's go watch
you want to run away again
Look at me, just a scholar
How can I escape Xiaoyue warrior
I'm sitting here alone and bored
okay, okay, okay
You're afraid, I won't even look just listen
I fear you?
You're afraid I'll slip away while I'm watching the show
If only Mochou were here
People with good kung fu are not afraid of others running away
go and watch then
no I wait, if I run away
I feel sorry for your elder sister to scold you
if you run
then my name isn't Xiaoyue
go
really
The play is so beautiful
walk, walk, hurry, hurry
Ji Xiaolan is really here
how do you figure?
"Ji five six people", they got it wrong
It should be the "five-Ji six-language"
Ji Ju Xiaolan's is ranked fifth, called five-Ji
It's probably a coincidence
he's sending us a signal
Fukangan, get someone right away
Yes