Mr. Ji, look
don't move
palace soldiers
How did the palace soldiers know we were here?
I do not know either
Fukangan
Mr. Ji really lured the traitor
It's you
I
Ji Xiaolan, you betrayed me
no i won't go
Mr. Ji is here, it's dangerous to stay here, go
she's not a traitor
She is she is here to whistleblow
Be careful
Mr. Ji, this is dangerous
Xiaoyue
take her away
The people of Yunzhou will never forgive you
Why are you in an ambush here, Mr Fu?
After Mochou was arrested, we knew that in her hand
was a very important roster
But torturing her in every possible way just doesn't say anything
So we guess
As long as there are two people who Mochou believes in, go
She'll be sure to tell where the roster is hidden
you are using me
any person Du Xiaoyue bringsMochou must also trust
I just needed to follow Mr. Ji
You can catch them without any effort
Fukangan I tell you
That roster is not a roster of rebels
Mr. Ji, how do you know
That's the evidence of corrupt officials
Rebels certainly won't be on the roster
Write down that you want to refute
They will definitely make up their own names to cover their identities.
Mr. Ji as a scholar, you are too naive
Lord Fu, I Mr Ji might be a scholar
But I can tell the difference between good and evil
Du Xiaoyue, beautiful
made a fool of Ji the scholar
It's hilarious
ok i don't explain anything to you
but i tell you
Du Xiaoyue, she's innocent, let it go
Let her go? Ji Xiaolan, you're just scholar
This kind of thing is out of your hands
Well, it's not up to me
But it's up to the emperor
emperor
yes if you don't let go
Ji must report to the emperor
Okay, do you want to see the emperor?
ok, congratulations, majesty
one's own will
Ji Huang is immoral and immoral
Take off the top and get rid of the post for the people
white lady
Lord, we should go back
what do you say
white lady, who is she
Since the lady, she is the white snake Bai Suzhen
How can the white snake be my mother?
this. servant...
If there was someone who could solve this riddle
That person would be Ji Xiaolan
Master, sevant understands
Lord Ji, please get up
You called wrong, Lord He
This is only the commoner Ji Xiaolan
Come back
Let him go
Folks and fathers, I am Du Xiaoyue
what to shout
Xiaoyue Xiaoyue
Corrupt officials harm the people
You have to help me find justice
Brother, your fireworks are going to explode
How did this happen?
Throw it out, throw it out, throw it out
Brother-in-law, I know you'll come to my rescue
Sister, I've come to help you
Xiaoyue go!. the evidence is important. Go!
sister
go fast
Xiaoyue
scum officer is you
give me the ledger in your hand
I'll tear you apart
It's would be a pity to break such a good vase
god is so unfair
Such a good bottle is still broken
go fast
chase them for me
These scum soldiers
search for me
Xu Xian
How come there are so many soldiers
leave me alone
If you are caught, you will be implicated too
it's okay no problem
Do you know who I am?
Aren't you the white lady?
I'm a rebel, the official government is chasing me
The government is arresting you
yeah, scared right?
Don't be afraid, don't be afraid, come with me
do you know Fahai
That old monk?
I learned invisibility from him
Invisibility
can this work
OK, don't look at it, it won't work
give me a careful search
Heavenly and Earthly
and lord why are you here
I'll tell you later
What's with this woman, Lord Heshen Mr. Heshen?
Why did the emperor save her?
The emperor is looking for the white lady
white lady
Lord Heshen. That account book
That girl has it
If it was seen by the emperor...
The account books are insufficient, we have to worry about Ji Xiaolan
Ji Xiaolan has been dismissed, he's no bother
The general is wrong
The emperor will be angry for a while
He will dismiss Ji Xiaolan for a while
He will find that he cannot do without Ji Xiaolan
I understand that Lord Heshen is saying. goodbye.
Ji Xiaolan what will you do next?
Xu Xian, you really know magic
Those people really didn't see
do you really believe
That's because I put you
That's because I wrapped you in a costume
Those soldiers saw me pressing on my robe
I thought I was a joke too
Han Ou for me
The original Song Wei is so stupid to buy those officers and soldiers
Waiyue, do you know Zimiaoshou?
Chuang Niang watch me play
Yan Niangzi is majestic
Don't you think I'm a bit like a white lady?
How can there be a white lady like you?
Satsuki
Xiaoyue, think about each other carefully
Is there any role in the play from the maid?
Looks a bit like I'm older than you
a bit like my age
It looks like you are younger than me
The spear is very similar to you
Like you, Mu Juecha Biqiu
The spear looks a lot like you, Mou Jibimi
seems to have
There is a difference between Ning and you
Ruthenium is with you
It's a bit like you
what is her name
I know the female Xiaoji
I know her name
I only know
She's digging
her baby name
ice
ma'am, are you alright
Sister, are you alright?
who is he with you
Who is he? are you talking nonsense with him?
who is he, you and him
Who is he and what are you talking about?
he is good
On his head is engraved the words "good man"
Sister, you don't know what he just saved
Ajier knew that he had just
The villain pretends to be a hero to save the beauty
price
Lie to your trust, you know that
Your plays are all in vain
moon
Xiaoyue girl, what is her name?
Xiaoyue girl, that white lady, she
she seems to
What are you talking about, let's go
What so much talk about me
moon girl
what is her nickname
go
i forgot
go fast
Mrs Fu
Wu Yuren, do you know
Haojuutian, did you know
绻
Someone is gossiping about you in front of Huangye
Someone is embarrassed in front of the emperor
Someone said your free time in front of the emperor
In front of the emperor
Someone came to Huangya to talk about your leisure time
gossip what gossip
You Renxiao secretly reported in front of the emperor
When Xiao Song Yunzhou
Haonong people warmly welcome
Saying that the two of you have an extraordinary relationship
Lord Ji Juxiaolan was a scholar at the time
Officer, this is the trick
It's not nothing to do
In fact, I have long hated Ji Xiaolan
But the emperor misunderstood himself
cut
Mr. Wu, this wearing a flower ling is afraid of prostitution
shared people
Tizhou grief
It's really unfair to lose the team and the official.
I can't leak it, but I'm wrong.
But Wu Gongren has one
Indifference to your self-confidence
Immediately drive Ji Xiaolan away
Don't leave this scourge anymore, understand?
what about the king
Come to Yunzhou without making a sound
what is he doing
Can't figure it out, can't figure it out
Ji Xiaolan, ah Ji Lan
Where are you now the head of a bachelor
Just a big pumpkin
one
It must be famous
Which Ji Xiaolan, which Ji Xiaolan
Lord Wu, this wind and lightning
how to invite you
Listen to your voice
Ji Ju Xiaolan, I've seen you look evil for a long time
The dagger is not right, the emperor is wise and wise
I have fired you
what
The academy is located in the center of the building, and people are not allowed to do so without permission.
Someone threw his things out at me
This is a saint's book, you dare
goddamn thing
Wu drunk dog sees people
God will punish you
That's my stuff, you give it back to me
Still the tiger skin belongs to me
Immediately report to Lord Heshen and Lord Fu Kangan
Just say I will take Ji Xiaolan
well repaired
Who dares to let him in the sedan
Stop the sedan for me
Look who is so bold
Mr. Heshen is
Lord Heshen is you
my own
I have kicked the surnamed Ji out of the academy
I even tore his umbrella
to make him happy
Mr. Ji, come and come, my sedan chair is big
First
Squeeze the two of us and sit
come, come, Mr. Ji
Lord Xie Heshen, return my things
Mr. Ji walks to have a drink with He Shen
come, please, please
Isn't this Lord Heshen and Ji Xiaolan mortal enemies?
Why did you come to help him again?
I really don't understand
Mr. Ji suffers from time to time
Warm up with a cup of Qiudan
This is the king's treasured wine
Lord Heshen took such a good deal
entertain two just fired
must be asking for something
good wine
Ji Lan is Ji Ju Xiaolan
nothing but you
What's wrong with Heshen dogs eating people with short mouths?
sir please see
what is this
Liao I
This is what I was about to ask you
This
Mr. Ji, who is famous all over the world, will surely know
Mr. Heshen, can I ask for advice?
where does this thing come from
than hook from
This thing involves a major case in Beijing
it's the only line
Sir please advise
please sir
This lock is called a longevity lock
worn by newborn babies
everywhere on the street
However
Gone
people come and come
Just now Mr.
However, Lord Heshen this piece of gold
It is indeed different from other golden locks
Honestly, Mr. Ji said
I don't know how much I've seen this
I don't see anything special.
let go
There's nothing here
I'm knocking the ashes
Don't knock on this and do it again
This cauldron is locked in a thousand pieces
But the goldsmiths who make locks
will leave a mark on themselves
mark
Did you see that there are two mountains?
This is a famous goldsmith in Yunzhou
Lin Xiaoquan's special mark
Mr. Ji, where does Lin Xiaoquan live now?
Now it's right for me
This Lin Xiaoquan is now living in the Confucian Temple.
Mr. Xie Ji's instructions
come and drink
Mr. Ji all the way
Mr. Heshen
let's go
goodbye
How come Ji Lan, Lord Heshen, is so obedient
I made him a beauty
Let him go back to Beijing to teach a few little Baylors
It's not a fart walk
Lord Heshen is worthy of being the contemporary Kongming
But dare not dare
But Ji Xiaolan is so
We can really sit back and relax
whistle
But the gang of disaster victims are making trouble.
Let the adults help
down these
As long as we let the emperor look for his life
He doesn't care about that
and adults
He Aiqing, you are not easy
Little things, He Lao, the emperor hangs
I've been thinking about this golden lock day and night, but I don't have any clues
Unexpectedly Heshen Aiqing
I can actually find this Lin Xiaoxiaoquan
I am surprised
Is such that
The minions arrived in Yunzhou, day and night to check the darkness
Finally found Lin Xiaoquan's
Then he looked at the cottage again and again
Only then did I know the mark on the golden lock
I'm very moved by how well Aiqing and Aiqing used a dagger.
Kill the slaves, the emperor finds
This filial dagger makes the world feel
and early
We must help the emperor to uncover the truth of his life
On the cave house
If He Shen Aiqing finds his biological mother
you are the first
Kill the slaves, this is the emperor Hong Fuqi
The slave is just a little dipped
The two masters are looking for Lin Xiaoxiao
how do you know
Lin Xiaoquan called the villain here
Lin Xiaoquan is just waiting here
How did he know we were coming
he
He said you were for the golden lock
He is waiting for you at the Guandi Temple next to the Confucius Temple
He is burdock
Bridge Xiaosha Zhifeng
This Lin Xiaoquan is simply a living fairy
Master lead the way
two gentlemen
Lin Xiaoquan said that the two can only advance one
It's a big deal, he knows we are
Who does he want to see
He said which of the two of you is uglier
Kyung-woo stays outside the door
That
Then you go in and get fat
Welcome to the Holy
Ji Xiaolan
the emperor
Lin Xiaoxiaoquan
What is Lin Xiaoquan?
This Lin Baquan was made up by the minister
you made it up
Then Heshen, he clearly told me
The emperor only uses this method
Heshen arsenic can lead you here
and ability to
You and Shen and Shen are bragging together
Ji Xiaolan
Do you know why I fired you?
Ten thousand
Long live please express
you only become a
to help me with the secret investigation
long live
I received a lot of esoteric ginseng in Beijing
Said to be the food for disaster relief here
Several
almost all of it was stolen
Up to the Governor and Governor down to Daofu Prefecture
collective corruption
I'm afraid this case is not easy to investigate.
I have already sent two batches of officials to investigate.
all in vain
A public inspection of such a case would be very effective
So, Your Majesty, you have to take it personally
So, Your Majesty, you decide to take your own personal clothes.
I only sent it when I arrived in Yunzhou
It's not that simple
I don't care where I go
Some people called the front station first to reveal
I will never see the truth
That's when it's inconvenient to be the emperor
The same goes for being an official
If you are a local government official, how can you not curry favor with you?
Food and wine plus beautiful women
sir
You can definitely reveal the truth for me
The minister Ji Juxiaolan will never fail my emperor
Yi Ji Zhen
In Ji Aiqing's opinion, where should one start?
The emperor returns to Beijing immediately
Local officials can relax their vigilance
they will reveal
just do that and come in with kun
Kyung-woo does this and kun and kun come in
three
Mr. Emperor Ji is also here
And Kunlin Koizumi
The slaves deeply feel that you are leaving Ji Xiaolan
suppress talent
Therefore, this method is specially used to make the ruler and minister meet as soon as possible.
Hurry up and get your car back to Beijing
Brother Huang, you are still not resting
yeah that ledger is missing
Write it down while my memory is still fresh
Officials protect each other, where can you go to sue you?
Unexpectedly, even Ji Xiaolan is so dark
Complain to the Imperial City
don't worry, you're afraid
I'll accompany Brother Ming to go up the knife mountain and down to Erhai
Who
I gonna go see
Brother Huang, officers and soldiers flee
Mochou go quickly
stand still stand
Brother Huang
Mochou go quickly
Satsuki and the brothers can't be taken away without anyone
After you leave, I break
If you don't win this case
All the people in the disaster area have to starve to death, hurry up
Brother Huang
Why don't you even listen to my words?
You, Enlun, the lotus tamarin, hope that you will suffer from Yiuril soon.
measure
He Shenqi Award
tell them to get out of the way
open
sill
don't hurt them
they are mine
Sister, why don't you let them go?
All back
go up
I don't know enough, I really don't know enough
I didn't see such a little trick.
ashamed
Heaven and Man
natural disaster
Aiqing, don't blame yourself
Ji Xiaolan, you are too presumptuous, this is for the emperor
And adults want to save the emperor
three seat pi
I'm the only one here
Are you sick
Liao sit or not
What's the matter with sitting or not sitting and getting out? Get up!
Ji Xiaolan
minister
how do we get out
There are three possible ways for the emperor to escape
count
I sit and you stand
Chai Diao No. 2
Let Lord Heshen come and beat me
beautiful you
Lord Heshen, you said
To save the emperor even if he died
of course
Then can you beat me on the back?
what does this have to do with this
Of course
He Kun hammer
i give him
hammer
work harder
Ji Xiaolan's third plan
The emperor pardons the guilt
I can't redeem this for the time being.
Are you excited?
Small
you two
Renhachi
You are actually called a jerk
Not only is it bad luck
I'm so sorry, my lord
You are crazy, I will fight with you
This dog is so bad to the next person
This scoundrel to Qiaotou
This dog officer is the next person
He's really bad.
fell
tell you as long as I'm out
I'm going to charge you thousands of miles
I'll let you never come back
Crazy, this Kyung-woo is crazy, I'll kill you
This is the third
When Ji Lan is here, you still want to make a name for yourself
stand up
You two listen to me
Lord, I'm here to stay
you have to follow
come and beat me
You, you have to pack me a cigar pot
Don't listen to the dog officer Xu Lai
We are all poor brothers
With my elbows turned inward, I'm here
Dog officer, don't try to bully you
You
don't listen to her
You two are not the same
They're all locked up with me in this pile of stinky fish
I can let whoever said it should be closed.
You little girl, you have a big mouth
Bambashi
what are you
If you want to let go, you have to be old
Bamboo says
what did you say
I told you we are coming today
Originally aimed at you, the dog officer
The next person had no intention of arresting him.
It was my sister who asked me to come and see
Squeak girl, they are both
Oops girl they two Kyungyo
You are arresting both of them now
you want to lie to me again
He's the Minister of War and they're both older than me
girl you got it right
You think I'm a three year old
Both of them are better than you
He beat your back just now
I stole it all outside the door
cricket me
Girl I'm telling the truth
you must believe me
emperor
forget me
Why am I not like the emperor?
Does the emperor look like you?
Bamboo Renqianfang
Look at the sturdy lifter
You really have eyesight when you lift the sedan chair
pretend
Then he looks at you like a minister
I see him
White and fat selling tofu
nothing but you
Girl, what are you looking at?
live
I'm here today to fight for the poor brothers
you two come with me
Nata
stay and go
three injustices
It's not fair, sir, I'm sitting here
Lord, I'm sitting here on the stinky fish
You're the next person to be at ease
Ma'am, I've checked it out
two of them
he
Neither is a servant
Look at your clothes
so back
We are for the big family
Gotta talk about the facade
In fact, inside and out
Kyungsoo looks so good
Sister, let them go, it's all suffering
Besides, this Xu Xian also saved me.
ok let them go
Xu Xian, I said no
May
Our elder sister is the most concerned about the poor brothers.
Our elder sister is the most concerned about the poor brother
Thank you ma'am and thank you ma'am
Then let's go
wait
Take some silver taels and send them to two brothers
The two of you sit here for one more time
Let you sit, just sit
sit
butler servant
Yes, what's the matter, Mrs.
Have you ever seen a housekeeper go to a servant?
butler serving servant
sister
Do you know how much this emerald finger is worth?
Erdan Huanghua
let them speak for themselves
I didn't expect you to be so confused
what are you talking about
I'm just dusting
Respectfully ask the Holy Master to sit first
Who knew that mother-in-law was so tricky
You
You are used to flattering emperors
Should I shoot you?
OK, OK, OK
He said I was flattering
How dare you three dog officials lie to me
Made me stink by our elder sister
I didn't lie to you, girl
I told you that the two of them are officials, you don't believe me
All three of you are not good
girl, let it go
Huang Keming ensures that he is okay and returns you wealth and glory
I won't be fooled by you
write what to write
Then my Ji Xiaolan's couplet is the best in the world
I come
Who wants you to write some bullshit couplets
Write a letter to Mr. Wu in Yunzhou Prefecture
Tell him to let it go
Yu rebuked
Otherwise, none of the three of you
You see I said they were there to save Huang Keming
price world
You are here to rescue Huang Ke
The one who just caught the court's dog officials?
just caught
You are so righteous
Girl, do you remember when you said
There is a play who plays the white lady
You want to know her nickname again, right?
Yeah, what's her nickname?
know inverse
I want to know but I won't tell you
Don't listen to her, how does she know what nickname
she brag
Who doesn't know her nickname
Our sister said
Tsukasa
I can't talk to you three dog officials.
travel with you
Does Huang Keming know what I'm here for?
When the adults come, they will die
grown ups
Wrong, I'm here to tell you a story
I said how old are you
What are you tinkering with? It's fishy and smelly
You put the emperor's safety first
Mr. Ji must be looking for something
Or the emperor knows me, the emperor
Still the king knows me
what do you want
That half golden lock
half slice
I have never disclosed any rumors
You can guess that I have this item
You must have revealed it.
How dare you not have the emperor's servants
Only you know my secret
Ga, who did you say?
The emperor's slave is guilty, the slave is guilty and deserves death
Yan Yu, it's okay
The emperor and the dog Kan is not only innocent
You should also reward him
you don't have to speak for him
Lord Heshen holding the half of the golden lock
come to me
falsely say
He didn't say it was the emperor's thing
but tell me yes
What is the evidence of the case, right?
You can guess that it's mine
Sanlong worships the executioner
The emperor and Lord Shen have worked with ministers a lot
house
I've never asked a minister because of my own affairs
only for the eyes of the king
He was willing to come to me and not be ashamed to ask
Then why did you come to ask me?
Since the emperor didn't tell me
It must be the emperor
How could Duke Ji Yun dare to ask?
Then why do you dare to ask me now?
Your Majesty, we are now at the end of our lives.
I won't be fat, as long as the Yunzhou government releases yellow
we'll be fine
The case of Huang Keming is now in the hands of Fukang An
Fukangan has a strong temperament and decides that Joe will be threatened by obedience
He will not let Huang Keming go
Najing finished Najing Youquan
He didn't know the hostage was the emperor
Please be born
they
Ding
Eight within
Thirty
Kwong
dog
dagger
news
hope
garbage
Yo hooligan
end
guard
Jun
Festival
almost
between
Jiu Jiwei
Dagger
right back
Ming Li
Shang Zhanwei
to
young
Dan
Bazai
Heart Dan
and
Only
one
Nine
圮
Bute
Seedling
Cangune
express the convexity
mixed protruding female call
Zoroastrian dry called Diao Neipian
Diao
Convex time uniform
Yi net spoon
Xigan is Diao
eat
begging
beuti
begging brother
Xian
brother-in-law
Yo
Makeup convex bull call
Spoon
When looking for an island
Diao when pretending to be convex
mango
Spoon
pong
malaria
qitun
busy
malaria
dragon nap
Qi
exactly this
Babe
insect
one
work
Street beef
convex
Warm core
dry bulge
benzyl calcium
Kanxin
Mu Cong Niu Yun
Mu Pingdiao
convex ox spoon
Do not slice when she is dry
Don't chase your teeth
coffin
one
Twenty
Qi
pong
Shi
shelter
Worker
go to Bei
Yo Xubei
scallop wind convex
Yi Gan
Mu Tuwu called no
Jue Concave Niu A Shao Nei
gong worm is
Inside the gong convex ox spoon
reputation
Shimaichi